[Music]
[Música]
k
k
ah
ah
[Music] [Music
[Música]
Oh
Oh
H [
H
ah
ah
Oh
Oh
[Music] [
[Música]
e [Music] [Music]
e
ti
ti
[Music] [Music]
[Música]
Oh
Oh
k [Music] [Music]
k
H [Music]
H
ha [Music] [Music] H [Music
ha
]
[Música]
B [Music]
B
ha [Music] ha
ha
[Music
[Música]
y
y
Good night
Buenas noches
people Good night how are you
gente Buenas noches qué tal estáis
family let's see eh Ugh I'm a bit in the [ __ ]
familia a ver eh Uf estoy un poco
today I'm a bit in the [ __ ] today Uh
hoy estoy un poco hoy en la [__] Eh
a lot of people in the comments on the
mucha gente en los comentarios del
lollipop news  wondering
noticiero de la piruleta preguntándome
what's wrong with you are you are serious you're
Qué te pasa Estás estás serio estás
unmotivated I'm like I've done something
desmotivado Estoy que he hecho una
crazy today I'm like I've done something crazy
locura hoy estoy que he hecho una locura
today
hoy
guys I
chavales he
got Good night just like I
cogido Buenas noches tal y como me
went to bed around 3 in the morning 4 I don't
acosté a eso de la 3 de la mañana 4 no
know what time it was around that time eh
sé qué hora sería a la hora por ahí eh
Lorena He moved he woke me up and I
Lorena Se movió me despertó y ya no me
couldn't sleep again the usual 6 7
podía dormir otra vez lo de siempre 6 7
8 I say I'm not going to bed anymore I don't do
8 digo ya no me acuesto ya no me hago
this to myself because it's the loop you go to sleep at
esto porque es el bucle te duermes a las
8 you get up at 6 at 5 5 in the
8 te levantas a las 6 a las 5 5 de la
afternoon not again at night and I'm
tarde otra vez por la noche no y estoy
holding on
aguantando
you I'm holding on
tú estoy aguantando
dude I'm holding on until it's
tío estoy aguantando hasta hasta que sea
a considerable hour eh the ideal would be to
una hora considerable eh lo ideal sería
hold on and do live also on
aguantar y hacer directo también en
telesalseo because I have songs there today
telesalseo porque tengo temas allí hoy
that I want to comment on the ideal would be to hold on
que que comentar lo ideal sería aguantar
here and then go to telesalseo and
aquí y luego irme para telesalseo y
hold on there or rather have dinner and hold on
aguantar allí o sea cenar y aguantar
there
allí
And from
Y a partir de
there on from there
ahí a partir de ahí
[Music]
[Música]
and tomorrow I'll start with the normal schedule
e mañana empez con con el horario normal
of a person not waking up at 10 to
de una persona no despertarte a las 10 a
going back to bed at
la volverte a acostar por la
night personal schedule
noche horario de persona horario de
personal schedule I'm not sleeping Maribel yes
persona estoy sin dormir Maribel sí
I'm not sleeping you can
estoy sin dormir
practically see the
prácticamente se te ve reflejadas las
screens reflected in your glasses watch out eh Watch out,
pantallas en las gafas ojo eh Ojo por
don't leak my
aquí no filtres las contraseñas de mi
bank account passwords here But anyway if I do it live here
bancaria Pero bueno si hago directo aquí
with you and I can't hold on for telesalseo that would be
con ustedes y no aguanto para telesalseo
fine that would be fine
ya estaría bien ya estaría bien en
really I mean
verdad
today it's a continuous session
o sea hoy sesión continua
eh The thing is Manuela, if
eh Es que lo que pasa Manuela que si
yesterday I got up at
ayer ya me levanté a las
6 and now it's 3 in the morning I lay down for
6 y ahora llega a las 3 de la mañana me
a while and 2 hours later
hecho un rato y a las 2 horas me
my wife wakes me up because she moves or I don't
despierta mi mujer porque se mueve o no
know if she got up she got up and I
sé si se levantó se levantó y ya no me
couldn't sleep anymore it was like I had
podía dormir era como si me hubiera
taken a chair boom and
echado una si silla pum y fresco
very fresh
fresquísimo
and when you start to get sleepy it's
y ya cuando te empieza a entrar sueño es
9 in the morning
las 9 de la mañana las
8 yes leia but today is a
8 sí leia pero es que hoy es una ocasión
special occasion chaiko Well that was already explained
especial chaiko Pues eso ya se explicó
tomorrow king tomorrow you're going to forgive me
mañana rey mañana me vais a perdonar
because yes eh my
porque eso sí
brain fails me a little more than
eh me falla un poco el coco más de la
usual I mean if it already fails me
cuenta O sea si ya me falla
habitually now with sleep it fails me
habitualmente ya con el sueño me falla
a little more than  account I fail the
un poco más de la cuenta me fallan la
syllable my
sílaba me me falla el
thought fails me everything fails me I have to
pensamiento me falla todo os tengo que
tell you
contar
something I have to tell you an exclusive
una os tengo que contar una exclusiva
okay the title is not clickbait
vale lo del título no es clickbait
eh look at you look at you
eh fíjate tú fíjate tú
that with the with the launch of the Channel
que que con el con el estreno del Canal
with the launch not the the the new name
con el estreno no el el el nuevo nombre
not the new name and and the
no el nuevo nombre y y la
new and the new life that we have now
nueva y la nueva vida que tenemos ahora
eh we have a pretty big exclusive coming
eh se nos viene una exclusiva bastante
eh
tocha eh
but pretty
pero bastante
big quite quite big eh
tocha bastante bastante tocha eh
pretty big I don't know if I'm going to I don't know
bastante tocha No sé si lo voy a no sé
if I'm going to
si lo voy a
tell it totally short circuit
contar modo corto circuito totalmente
dude totally and also I think that in the
tío totalmente y además creo que en el
news today it shows eh in the news
noti hoy se me se me nota eh en el noti
today it shows Because also eh what
hoy se me nota Porque además eh lo que
happened to me with the news today
me ha pasado también con los noti hoy
that luare is doing badly is doing badly
que luare está malillo está malillo
luare seems to be recovering
luare ya parece que se va recuperando
because he just sent me some stuff for
porque me acaba de mandar cosillas para
now for the live but today's news about
ahora para el directo pero el noti de de
the kids that I didn't want to
hoy de la chavalería que no quería
leave you today without a newscast could have
dejaros hoy sin noticiero podría haberos
left you without a newscast and have but today
dejado sin noticiero y haberme pero hoy
eh to debut the new change I wanted to
eh para estrenar el nuevo cambio quería
have a newscast today and  damn I got it I
hoy tener noticiero y [__] que me lo he
got a newscast pum pum pum pum
sacado me he sacado un noticiero pum pum
so between one thing and another
pum pum entonces entre una cosa y otra
today I have something that is
hoy llevo una que
amazing today I have something that is amazing I
flipas hoy llevo una que flipas he
put in the title that the exclusive
puesto en el título que la exclusiva
about Willy Rex no
sobre Willy Rex no
HM what do I say it I already say it or is it that you wo
HM qué hago la digo ya la digo ya o es
n't see it now it's an announcement I mean today it's not
que tampoco verás tú ahora es un anuncio
eh today it's not as such the bomb today is the
eh hoy no es como tal la bomba hoy es la
exclusive that also you're already
exclusiva que además ya me estáis
putting me more or less you're
poniendo de más o menos me estáis
putting something there in the chat okay I'm going
poniendo algo ahí en el chat vale lo voy
to tell it I'm going to tell it and that's it and
a contar lo voy a contar y ya está y
when people start coming in Well let them find
cuando vaya entrando la gente Pues que
out let them go further back and let them
se entere que vaya más para atrás y que
find out okay but it's a bomb
se vaya enterando vale pero es una bomba
eh it's a
eh es una bomba
good bomb Let's see I'm not going to tell you too
buena A ver no voy a deciros todavía
much information yet okay not to give you today
muchos datos vale para no daros lo hoy
but what I am going to tell you
pero lo que sí os voy a decir
is for you to be very aware of the
es para que estéis muy pendientes del
Channel so that you have the bell
Canal para que estéis con la campanita
activated so that you are subscribed not
activada para que estéis suscritos no
with the bell activated what I am
con la campanita activada lo que sí os
going to tell you is the
voy a decir es lo
following
siguiente
delox has recorded
delox ha grabado
a podcast today with  Willy
hoy un podcast con Willy
Rex
Rex
okay the guy with glasses called me this afternoon
vale me llamó el gafas este mediodía
and he
y
called me this
me llamó este
afternoon I didn't know that today I had a
mediodía Yo no lo sabía que hoy había
date with Willy Rex and he recorded it
quedado con Willy Rex y lo ha grabado
okay Not only that I recorded with
vale No solamente que haya grabado con
Willy Rex is that this is going to be the
Willy Rex es que ya ese va a ser el
last podcast I think he told me Yes
último podcast creo que me ha dicho Sí
that is going to be the last podcast of the year
ese va a ser el último podcast del año
okay
vale
Eh I'm not going to tell you the day it's uploaded
Eh no voy a deciros el día que se sube
because he doesn't want me to say it in
porque no quiere el que lo diga por si
case he gets his fingers caught okay you
acaso se pilla los dedos vale
know how it is The madness of that no that it will
ya sabéis Cómo es la La locura de eso no
last 3 4 hours go find out how long it
que durará 3 4 horas vete to sab lo que
lasts no and it will be and it will be an edition that
dura no y será y será una edición que te
pisses you off not the teaser that in itself the
caga no el teaser que ya de por sí el
teaser takes a long time
teaser tarda en una jartar
no but he does have the
no pero sí que tiene ya planeado el
next podcast planned that comes
siguiente podcast que va
after it okay pay attention to this eh pay attention to the
detrás vale atentos a esto eh atentos al
detail that I'm only going to repeat it
dato que solamente lo voy a repetir una
once and also I'm very tired and I'm
vez y además estoy muy cansado y estoy
very in love
muy enorado
I'm in [ __ ] Parra today eh I'm in
estoy en la [__] Parra hoy eh estoy en
[ __ ] Parra
la [__] Parra
eh I'm in [ __ ] Parra But anyway I'm
eh estoy en la [__] Parra Pero bueno os
going to explain it to you and and and it's done tomorrow you can
lo voy a explicar y y y ya está mañana
watch it again and if  I'm fresher
lo volvéis a ver y si estoy más fresco
tomorrow I'll tell you
mañana os lo digo otra
again the thing is
vez la movida Es
that today cinema was recorded
que hoy se ha grabado
okay today the Willy Rex podcast was recorded
vale hoy se ha grabado el podcast de
okay but the thing is that delox already has
vale pero es que es que delox ya tiene
planned not recorded but planned
planeado que no grabado pero sí planeado
okay the next podcast that comes after
vale el siguiente podcast que va detrás
and the next podcast that comes after I'm not going
y el siguiente podcast que va detrás no
to say who it is
voy a decir quién es
okay but it's a
vale pero es una
gossip person or rather a
persona del salseo o sea persona del
gossip person let's call it that okay and the
salseo vamos a llamarlo así vale y el
other podcast not Willy's but the other
otro podca no el de Willy sino el otro
podcast has a Plus a bonus
podca tiene un Plus un bonus
Track okay that will come that's separate
Track vale eso ya vendrá eso es aparte
that he told me and here I
eso me la ha contado y yo aquí me he
wanted to hit the nail on the head that I
querido pegar el el pego tillo de que os
warned you about okay but the thing is that in the in
avisé vale pero es que en el en el en el
today's
de hoy de
Willy's today's Willy's it
Willy el de hoy de Willy
's an outrage he's been telling me
es una barbaridad me ha estado contando
some headlines and it's a [ __ ]
algunos titulares y es una puñetera
outrage it's a [ __ ] outrage eh I
barbaridad es una puñetera barbaridad eh
mean next week is that topic
o sea la semana que viene es el tema ese
or come on but I'll tell you like this
o vamos pero os lo digo así la semana
next week I'm going to see who it is wait a minute some [ __ ]
viene voy a ver quién es un momento me
is calling me at this
están llamando a esta
time it's
hora
next week's topic is  the topic no no Today it's not coming out of
viene es el tema no no Hoy no sale de
creator now I'll tell you now I'll tell you
creator ahora os cuento ahora os cuento
something important which is the it's the
una cosa importante que es la es la
bomb and it's the exclusive okay it's the
bomba y es la exclusiva vale la es el
topic eh I mean but it's the topic it's the topic
tema eh o sea pero es el tema es el tema
of what we're going to do we're not going to that if it's
de que vamos de que no vamos que si lo
released today cool he
estrenar hoy
has to retouch the rewind and
molón tiene que retocar el rewind y
put
meter
things in okay I mean it's the topic of
cosas vale o sea es el tema de la semana
next week of all the channels and everything
que viene de todos los canales y de todo
kiki and Twitter and And all the live gossip
kiki y de Twitter y Y de todos los
and everything okay it's it's
directos del salseo y de todo vale
the host
es es la [__]
okay it's the host
vale es la [__]
okay And
vale Y
also in the salsera I mean
además en la salsería O sea
here here
aquí
you know what's going on
aquí sabéis Qué pasa
here let's see you know what's going on
aquí a ver sabéis qué pasa
here well here here
aquí pues
what happens is that
aquí aquí lo que pasa es que se estrena
the
el
teaser is released here the
teaser aquí se estrena el
teaser is released I don't know what day it is I don't know what day it is I'm
tser no sé qué día es no sé qué día es
not going to tell you a day because because you do
no os voy a decir un día porque porque
n't know you don't even know But
no lo saben no lo saben siquiera Pero
well in a few
bueno en unos
days in a few
días en unos
days Here the teaser is released I'm not going to see the teaser
días Aquí se estrena el teaser yo no voy
eh I'm not going to see the
a ver el teaser eh yo no voy a ver el
teaser before you guys I'm going to see it
teaser antes que ustedes yo lo voy a ver
eh with you guys I mean so that the reaction
eh con ustedes o sea para que reacción
is
sea
real  the taser is released here like
real el taser se estrena aquí como
when we did the
cuando hicimos lo
Nimu thing Caesar as far as Saturday I don't
nimu César tanto como para el sábado no
think so let's see I'm telling you it's
lo creo a ver te digo que te digo que es
in a few days but as far as
en unos días pero tanto como para el
Saturday don't keep in mind that tomorrow is
sábado no ten en cuenta que mañana es
Friday no no for Saturday the taser is not here
viernes no no para el sábado el taser no
but come on Not much longer
está pero vamos No mucho más
luare my son you missed a lot yesterday
luare hijo mío te perdiste mucho ayer
no
no
eh Let's see before Christmas there's no time
eh A ver antes de navidad no da tiempo
chaico Christmas is on Sunday well
chaico la Navidad es el domingo bueno
Sunday on Christmas Eve But before no
domingo en la Nochebuena Pero antes no
man but let's go there there
hombre pero vamos ahí
or so a few
ahí o sea unos
days Let's see I don't know Monday Tuesday Wednesday I
días A ver no sé lunes martes miércoles
don't know the truth no no no I'm not going to
No lo sé la verdad no no no no os voy a
tell you a day because they don't know either and
decir un día porque tampoco lo saben ni
they don't I don't remember if they edited
ellos no me acuerdo si primero editaban
the 4 hours first and once they have
las 4 horas y ya una vez que tengan
edited the 4 hours they choose the
editar las 4 horas Ya eligen el el
teaser of course I imagine No of course first they
teaser claro me imagino No claro primero
edit the big ones and then they choose the
editan lo grande y luego eligen el
teaser I understand I don't remember eh I don't remember
teaser entiendo no me acuerdo eh No me
Eh I don't remember if the other time
acuerdo Eh no me acuerdo si la otra vez
they edited the teaser first but by
editaron primero el teaser pero yo por
logic I understand that
lógica entiendo que primero lo editan
the big ones edit it first and then they know what they're going to
los gordos y ahí ya saben que van a
take for the teaser but  the
[__] para para el al teaser pero el
teaser premieres here exclusively eh
teaser se estrena aquí en exclusiva eh
the teaser premieres here exclusively
el teaser se estrena aquí en exclusiva
with delox here with us
con delox aquí con nosotros
obviously
evidentemente
with delos here with us commenting on
con delos aquí con nosotros comentando
the gossip that he's worth it that he has to
el chisme que ya le vale que ya tiene
come you're looking at the magnification of my
venir estáis mirando el aumento de mis
glasses Well the magnification of my glasses blind blind blind
lentes Pues el aumento de mis lentes
crystal crystal of a
de cristal de una
Berlingo so that was what I
berlingo así que eso era lo que os he
put on Twitter that I had to
puesto en Twitter que os tenía que
tell you that I had a
contar que tenía una
bomb and it's a bomb eh it's a bomb or so yes yes it
bomba y es una bomba eh es una bomba o
seems
sea si ya si ya os parece
good when you know the
bueno cuando sepáis los
headlines don't believe that it
titulares sea no os vayáis a creer que
's a cryptocurrency podcast Eh well I do
es un podcast de criptomoneda Eh bueno
n't know if there will be a cryptocurrency part
no sé si habrá una parte de criptomoneda
but at least at least what
pero por lo menos por lo menos lo que
we
nosotros
want well he hasn't told me anything I
queremos pues me no me ha dicho nada
think he hasn't realized I think he has
Creo que no se ha dado cuenta creo que
n't realized uh if he was
no se ha dado cuenta est si estaba hoy
busy today with him with Willy
liado él con el con el Willy
r so so that's how
r así
things are
así que así está la cosa
you
tú
the truth is that I was very happy
la verdad que me he puesto muy contento
today when he
hoy cuando me lo ha
told me because December
dicho porque diciembre
[Music]
[Música]
is December is so-so
está diciembre está regulín
eh Jordi Wi's podcast  auron will not be
eh el podcast de Jordi Wi auron no será
this year it's that auron is not by the
este año es que auron no está por la la
her voice
voz de ella
anywhere
ningún a ninguna parte
man it's that auron goes auron has already gone to the
tío es que auron va auron ya ha ido al
Channel that he had to go to which was
Canal que tenía que ir que era el de
Javi
Javi
Oliveira's and there is his interview ok
oliveira y ahí está su entrevista vale o
so the auron podcast is where it has to be
sea el podcast de auron está en donde
ok on Javi
tiene que estar vale en el Canal de Javi
Oliveira's Channel ok you ponies Javi
oliveira vale ustedes ponis Javi
Oliveira and auron and there it appears and
oliveira y auron y ahí te aparece y
calm and calm ok let's see things
tranquilo y tranquilo vale a ver cositas
Well apart from apart from apart from
Bueno aparte de aparte de aparte de
apart
aparte de aparte
from some little things that they are
de algunas cosillas que me están
putting me in the group and now we see it and
poniendo en el grupo y ahora lo vemos y
now we
ahora lo
see it well I'm going to start with two or three
vemos pues voy a empezar con dos o tres
seeds that I had here prepared just in
semillas que tenía yo aquí preparado por
case luar no didn't come
si acaso luar no no venía
and and we'll see it says with
y y vamos viendo dice con
Dallas or
Dallas o sea
Nico the interview with Dallas but about
Nico la entrevista con Dallas pero de la
Jordi's It's
de Jordi No pasa
okay
nada
heal yourself you can do it heal yourself you can
cúrate puedes hacerlo cúrate que puedes
do it Well look, today searching for
hacerlo Pues fíjate que hoy buscando tem
miles today searching for miles I
millas hoy buscando tem millas me
found this and I was like
encuentro con esto y me Me he quedado
wow but I hadn't heard from
digo [__] pero yo no volvía a saber de
this kid again for many,
este chaval de hacía ya muchos años
many years or so this  boy was a
muchísimos años o sea este chico era un
boy and he's still a boy this boy
chico y sigue siendo un chico este chico
is a youtuber
es un youtuber
who recorded with with with Stone his name is
que grababa con con con Stone se llama
he this one recorded with mega glowen okay
él este grababa con mega glowen vale
luare with mega glowen
luare con mega glowen
with with ileo blo and with these people no and it
con con ileo blo y con esta gente no y
turns out that he has uploaded a
resulta que ha vuelto hoy a subir un
video again today because they have pulled a
vídeo porque la han la han metido una
huge scam on him Gabrielo a kiss handsome
estafa gorda gabrielo un beso guapísimo
a kiss What happens is that it is true I am
un beso Lo que pasa que sí que es verdad
going to watch the video with you because in
voy a ver el vídeo con ustedes porque en
the news I have told it without without the video I have
el noti lo he contado sin sin el vídeo
told it with documentation and such
lo he contado con documentación y tal
that I had found on Twitter but
que me había encontrado en Twitter pero
I am missing data man let's see what you get
me faltan datos tío a ver ustedes qué
from here you will
pilláis de aquí
see
verá
What's up
Qué pasa
silly How are you? I hope
bobitos Qué tal Cómo estáis Espero que
everything is okay Welcome to a new video
todo bien Bienvenidos a un nuevo vídeo
on Channel 10 years later almost nothing
en el Canal 10 años después casi nada
but I am the same Well a little more
pero soy el mismo Bueno un poquito más
Sugar papi no We confirm We confirm
Sugar papi no Confirmamos Confirmamos
How strange everything No yes I I don't know why he
Qué raro todo No sí yo yo no sé por qué
stopped uploading videos I don't know if he
dejo de subir vídeo no sé si es que
would be doing some kind of some
estaría haciendo algún tipo de alguna
race okay I didn't even know this that he
carrera vale ni siquiera sabía esto de
had a brand and a clothing store
que tenía una marca y una tienda de ropa
and so on and that he was completely
y demás y que estaba completamente
focused on that so that you can see that
centrado en eso para que ustedes veáis
many  sometimes YouTube
que muchas veces YouTube
eh to live off YouTube or to live off
eh para vivir de YouTube o para vivir de
this You don't necessarily have to be
esto No necesariamente tienes que ser
Our on Play I mean there are a lot of people who do it
Our on Play O sea hay mucha gente que se
well okay because through
lo monta bien vale porque a través de
YouTube well maybe they get to
YouTube pues Consigue a lo mejor
promote their store promote their brand and it's
impulsar su tienda impulsar su marca y
on YouTube more or less with some
está en Youtube más o menos con unas
visits okay ok throwing and eh but he
visitas bien vale tirando y eh pero
has an Instagram account with a
tiene una cuenta Instagram con una
store that well it's going away it's going away he's getting
tienda que pues se va
rich surely
Se va se vao se forra seguramente no
we're not talking about an account we're
estamos hablando de una cuenta estamos
talking about an
hablando de una
account of
cuenta
a million or rather an account of a
de de un millón o sea una cuenta de un
million one and he had a physical store Look it's that
millón una y tenía tienda física Mira es
in the news I was wondering I say I think he
que en el noticiero me preguntaba yo
has a physical store because
digo creo que tiene tienda física porque
he talks about how they took the key from him
él habla de que le quitan la llave
too, I mean The kid creates an account
también o sea El chaval Crea una cuenta
okay it's a kind of meme account
vale es una cuenta medio cuenta meme
okay What happens is that he publishes phrases he
vale Lo que pasa que publica frases é le
likes to write phrases or they write them
gusta escribir frases o se las escriben
in his bathroom or whatever I don't understand it
en su baño o lo que sea no lo entiendo
very well or he goes around the
muy bien o va é por los bates por los
bathrooms of businesses taking pictures
baños de los negocios haciendo fotos
but the account is basically very
pero la cuenta básicamente es muy
simple what he publishes are phrases Okay
sencilla lo que publica son frases Vale
and he rocks I mean but he rocks
y lo Peta o sea pero que lo Peta que
the account has a million a million
tiene la cuenta un millón de un millón
followers
de seguidores
well I'm here  a little weird I'm
bien estoy aquí un poco raro se me he
all worried and But anyway I'm wearing the
rallado por todo y Pero bueno llevo la
shirt as you can see the official one is still here
camiseta como veis la oficial sigue aquí
in one piece it keeps getting in me It's that I
de una pieza me sigue entrando es Es que
take care of this little body and nothing
cuido este cuerpito serrano y nada
audience Well, here we are I have
audience Pues nada aquí estamos traigo
a somewhat serious video the truth So I
un vídeo un poco serio la verdad Así que
have to get serious
me tengo que poner serio
dude Let's get on with the serious video
macho Vamos allá con el vídeo serio el
today's video is basically the story
vídeo de hoy es básicamente la historia
of you [ __ ] I said that in other words
de te lo [__] dije que en otras palabras
Or phrases it is and I'm going to tell you this
O frases es y voy a contaros esta
story for you and for me for you
historia por vosotros y para mí por
because x buer the other day
vosotros porque al x buer el otro día
made a video And he said that this year with
hizo un vídeo Y puso que en este año con
his clothing brand he has generated 1.3
su marca de ropa ha generado 1,3
million
millones de
euros the other day on teles
euros es que el otro día en la en teles
salcero we were talking there are some
salcero estuvimos hablando hay algunos
of these small youtubers that have
youtubers de estos pequeños que han
come out and
salido y
such and they do it well they have their
tal y se lo montan bien tienen su
stable fixed community maybe they don't
comunidad estable fija a lo mejor no
have many viewers but they have
tienen muchos espectadores pero tienen
their stable fixed community
su comunidad estable fija
with their fixed members and their more or
e con sus miembros fijos y su más o
less their super chat and so on and that they have you
menos su super chat y demás y que tenga
know and it is maintained and it is
sabes y se va manteniendo y se va
maintained I love that account I didn't know it
manteniendo amo esa cuenta no sabía que
was his I love it Well look mik you
era de él me encanta Pues fíjate mik ti
a million people be it  it's that a
a un millón de personas sea es que un
million a million followers on
millón un millón de seguidores en
Instagram is a lot eh a million I think I think
instagram es mucho eh un millón Creo que
Dallas has it I mean look at
creo que lo tiene el Dallas o sea fíjate
you Dallas With the years he's been
tú el Dallas Con los años que lleva
doing this and with the number of
dedicándose a esto y con la de
subscribers he has I mean it's [ __ ]
suscriptores que tiene o sea es una [__]
crazy That you create an account of
locura Que tú te crees una cuenta de
tiles not phrases on the tiles and you
azulejos no frases en los azulejos y te
get a million Followers of course the
pille un millón de Seguidores claro la
store must have done well and he must have said
tienda le habrá ido bien y habrá dicho
damn haby I recorded a video I'm going to
[__] haby a grabado yo vídeo me voy a
put the end Well then there are many of
poner final Bueno pues habéis muchos de
you who have grown up with me you
vosotros habéis crecido conmigo me
have supported me throughout all these years
habéis apoyado durante todos estos años
through thick and thin and I think
en las buenas y en las malas y creo que
you deserve to know what I'm going to
os merecéis conocer lo que os voy a
tell you on the other hand because well Many
contar por otro lado porque bueno Muchos
of you have asked me I
de vosotros me habéis preguntado incluyo
also include not only my followers but
también no solo a mis seguidores sino
also my friends many friends who
también a mis amigos muchos amigos que
in the end are all my friends within reason
al final sois todos mis amigos dentro de
eh You have asked me and I
lo que cabe eh Me habéis preguntado y yo
literally do not have the time
literalmente no tengo tiempo material
to tell each of you the story eh
para contaros la historia a cada uno eh
separately I literally cannot
por separado literalmente no puedo
do it it would tear me apart
hacerlo me me me me desgarraría por
inside I think I will do it and then well
dentro Yo creo hacerlo e entonces bueno
if I make a video in the end I will tell you  I tell
si hago un vídeo al final os lo cuento a
everyone at once and in that sense I am
todos a la vez y en ese sentido soy
efficient which is how I like to be and on the
eficiente que es como me gusta ser y por
other hand I also do it for myself eh You already
otro lado lo hago también para mí eh Ya
know me I am a natural person eh
me conocéis soy una persona natural eh
transparent I am direct and now I want to
transparente Soy directo y ahora quiero
talk to you about my feelings once again I
hablaros de mis sentimientos una vez más
want to use the networks to
quiero utilizar las redes para para para
express myself and to tell you something um and in
expresarme y para contaros algo em y en
that sense I think it will also
ese sentido creo que a mí también me va
help me that you all know what has
ayudar que que conozcáis todos lo que ha
happened that it is about time So let's go
pasado que ya va siendo hora Así que
with it as many of you already know I
vamos con ello como ya sabéis muchos de
[ __ ] told you it was born in the
vosotros te lo [__] dije nació en el
bathroom of my house with the savings from
baño de mi casa con los ahorros de
YouTube because I put down the deposit on a house
YouTube pues di la entrada para una casa
on the outskirts of Madrid and well I knew
a las afueras de Madrid y bueno yo sabía
from the beginning that I wanted a bathroom
desde el principio que quería un baño
painted and signed by my friends so that's how
pintado y firmado por mis amigos así que
the concept was born a little whenever
así nació un poco el concepto siempre
my a bathroom painted and signed by
que mis un baño pintado y firmado por
my friends I mean the guy with the savings
mis amigos o sea el tío con los ahorros
from YouTube
de YouTube
eh
eh
damn he
[__]
has 280
tiene 280
subscribers let's
suscriptores a
see 280 subscribers let's see you can
ver 280 suscriptores está a ver puedes
live with 280,000 subscribers
vivir con 280.000 suscriptores
obviously
evidentemente
but but of course giving it his all but the
pero pero claro dándole caña pero es que
guy the way of working on
este chico la forma de trabajar en
YouTube a few years ago was not the
YouTube hace hace unos años no era la
same as it is now  there are people
misma que ahora que está la gente en
live extract a video Every day this
directo extracto un vídeo Cada día este
kid Maybe he uploaded a couple of
chaval A lo mejor te subía un par de
videos a week I think it was eh I think I do
vídeos a la semana creo que era eh creo
n't know maybe I'm freaking out
no lo sé a lo mejor me estoy flipando
but of course I understand that being a
pero claro entiendo que al ser un
super white content because he
contenido como super blanco porque él
made his blogs with his friends he met up
hacía sus blogs con sus amigos se reunía
with friends I don't know what And then
con los amigos no sé qué Y entonces
of course the brands call you more and maybe
claro te llaman más las marcas y a lo
Coca-Cola calls you and pays you 3000
mejor te llama coca-cola y te paga 3000
because you post a picture with a
porque pongas una fotografía con una
Coca-Cola t-shirt seeing you a
camiseta de coca-cola viéndote un
Coca-Cola in a eh on a terrace you know
coca-cola en una eh en una terraza sab
then
entonces
Eh well yes I know if it was bought yes yes
Eh bueno si se si se ha comprado si si
with that he got the entrance it's that he has it he's
con eso tuvo la entrada es que lo tiene
not going to make it up but what
no se lo va a inventar pero lo que me
catches my attention is that he bought you a
llama la atención es que te compre una
new house and you tell your friends to
casa nueva y le digas a tus colegas que
sign the bathroom come on here if you have the
te firmen el baño vamos aquí si tenéis
balls to step into my house any My
huevo de pisar mi casa alguno Mi casa
new house Eh you don't clean your feet in the
nueva Eh no os limpiais los pies en el
being
ser
could friends were all drunk all stoned or
pudo amigos iban todo pedo todo fumados
whatever at home or wanted to get me into
o lo que fuera en casa o quisieran
something well they knew that they had the
liarme alguna pues sabían que tenían los
markers in the bathroom and  my bathroom was
rotuladores en el baño y mi baño estaba
painted with tremendous absurdity I who
pintado de tremendas absurde yo que
had always written things the typical in
siempre había escrito cosas lo típico en
the notes of the phone And such But every time I
las notas del móvil Y tal Pero cada vez
lost my phone well eh they went to
que perdía móvil pues eh se iban a la
[ __ ] and suddenly like
[__] y de repente pues como que
someone gives me a phrase in front of the ba and
alguien me una frase enfrente del bá y
Fu like oysters And if I paint my phrases
Fu como ostras Y si pinto mis frases
here and like that I have them come on it rents me
aquí y así las tengo tal venga me renta
and I started to paint the phrases that
y empecé a pintar las frases que se me
occurred to me one of the first phrases in
ocurrían una de las primeras frases de
fact That I painted I remember that it was from the
hecho Que pinté recuerdo que fue de la
song princesses of sloth which is
canción de princesas de pereza que es
a song that unites us a lot right
una canción que nos une mucho verdad
audience and nothing that I remember that I uploaded it
audience y nada esa recuerdo que la subí
like to my account eh And princess What
como a mi cuenta eh Y princesa Qué
laziness princess What laziness or princess of
pereza princesa Qué pereza o princesa de
sloth let's see Perea let's
pereza a ver Perea a
see
ver
Perea is a
Perea es un
group I follow one I continue looking for a smile
grupo sigo una sigo buscando una sonrisa
suddenly in a bar a drag of something
de repente en un bar una calada de algo
that can get me high a movie that manages to
que me pueda colocar una película que
make me cry
consiga hacerme llorar
Yeah change one I don't believe anything for I
Ajá cambiar un No me creo nada por te
love you kid yeah
quiero chaval sí
[ __ ] No Let's see I can't play because it's on
[__] No A ver no puedo al Play porque
me but I know the lyrics
me me peta pero la la conozco esta letra
eh I mean what I don't know
eh o sea lo que no me lo que no caigo
now is the tone and I uploaded it from  post and
ahora es el tono y la subí de post y de
suddenly people liked it
repente como que a la gente le molaba
more than my [ __ ] face you know and it was like
más que mi [__] cara sabes y fue como
Wow, since I'm really into
Vaya pues yo que soy mucho de hacerme
counting, I created a new account eh To
cuentas me hice una nueva cuenta eh Para
have like all the phrases there
tener como todas las frases ahí
compiled and suddenly dude
recopiladas y de repente pues tío me
passed me by on the left and that's how it was born a
pasó por la izquierda y así nació un
little bit well that's how it was born I [ __ ] told you I said
poco bueno así nació te lo [__] dije
freak out at the time of I mean he passes by on the
flipa al tiempo de o sea le pasa por la
left an account of phrases you
izquierda una cuenta de de frases tú
art I [ __ ] told you I decided to share the
arte lo [__] dije decidí compartir la
idea and the project with a Well,
idea y el proyecto con un Bueno pues
life partner that I had until very
compañero de vida que tenía hasta hace
recently and together we set up well the whole
bien poco y juntos montamos pues todo el
e-commerce okay I mean the friend is not a
e-commerce vale o sea el colega no es un
friend the one that uh with whom he shares the
colega el que eh con el que comparte la
store Of course I understand that it
tienda Claro entiendo que
is I understand that it is a boyfriend
es entiendo que es un novio
no let's see Well a life partner
no a ver Bueno un compañero de vida
could be a roommate a friend
podría ser un compañero de piso un amigo
but I understand that I understand that it is a
pero entiendo que entiendo que es un
boyfriend no pass Thank you very much honey
novio no pas Muchísimas gracias corazón
what are you doing here with the
qué haces por aquí ya con los
kids it's not the most relevant thing But
chavales no es lo más relevante Pero
well it's that of course I don't understand how
bueno es que claro no pille como de
suddenly someone grabs you and does that to you I mean
repente alguien te coge y te hace eso o
because what they do now is change the
sea porque lo que hace ahora es cambiar
ownership of the business and take it
de de propiedad el el negocio y se lo
away I mean but it's  literally a robbery
quita o sea pero es literalmente un robo
if this is tone can
si esto es tone lo puede
prove it somehow he can prove
probar de alguna manera él puede probar
for
por
example Well let's continue seeing the
ejemplo Bueno vamos a seguir viendo la
story And now I tell you I'm going to be
historia Y ahora os comento os voy a
here giving solutions without you having
estar aquí dando soluciones sin que lo
heard it okay but I understand that it
hayáis escuchado vale pero entiendo que
is a boyfriend I understand that it is a couple
es un novio entiendo que es una pareja
eh And what you know as Well the
eh Y lo que conocéis como Bueno pues la
back part is not of the [ __ ] I said at the
parte de atrás no de de lo [__] dije al
beginning everything was very nice but with
principio todo era muy bonito pero con
the passage of time well as
el paso del tiempo pues como
unfortunately often happens in
desgraciadamente muchas veces ocurre las
relationships you go what things go they go they
relaciones pasas qué cosan se van se van
start my relationship eh with this
empezando mi relación eh con esta
person it was getting worse until this
persona fue yendo a peor hasta este
summer when things exploded what
verano que ya pues la cosa explotó qué
happened I don't understand what it talks
es lo que sucedió no entiendo que habla
about a romantic relationship it couldn't
de una relación sentimental no podría
be a friendship but I think that I think that is not
ser de amistad pero creo que creo que no
the case I think that is what was happening
es el caso cre que es lo que pasaba
give us context for me the reason why we have been
danos contexto para mí el motivo por el
separating
cual nos hemos nos hemos ido separando
Yes it is that we have eh principles eh and
Sí es que tenemos eh principios eh y
different values I also believe that it
valores diferentes creo también que no
is not a problem to maintain a
es ningún problema para mantener una
relationship to have different principles or values
relación tener principios O valores
as long as there is
diferentes siempre y cuando exista un
mutual respect for those ideas and values I
mutuo respeto a esas ideas y valores Es
mean, I don't care if we are different
decir me da igual que seamos diferentes
If you respect me as I am and I
Si tú me respetas como soy y yo te
respect as you are We are not going to have
respeto como eres No vamos a tener
any problems we will always reach
ningún problema llegaremos siempre a
agreements as long as we both
acuerdos siempre y cuando los dos
want and that was, I think, what
queramos y eso fue yo creo lo que
ideological differences I understand here
diferencias ideológicas entiendo yo aquí
uh what failed honestly not on my
eh lo que falló honestamente no por mi
part in fact that I am the typical person
parte de hecho eso soy la típica persona
who in order to reach an agreement then
que con tal de llegar a un acuerdo pues
sacrifices on their part You know I have always
sacrifica de su parte Sabes Yo siempre
preferred to have a friend have a
he preferido tener un amigo tener una
partner and have a person than to be
pareja y tener una persona a tener la
right the truth is that I think it is not
razón la verdad es que creo que no me
worth it for me to be right and lose a
compensa tener la razón y perder una
person but well It is true to a
persona pero bueno Es cierto que hasta
certain limit No because then I am the
cierto límite No porque luego soy la
typical person who swallows
típica persona que se lo va tragando
everything and ends Well here is the translation
todo y acaba Bueno aquí la traducción
that I make of what he is saying
que yo hago de esto que está contando
eh also I watch this video a bit
eh además Este vídeo lo veo un poco
also to vent and uh for
también para desahogarse y para eh que
the other to see it no e because of 10
el otro lo vea no e porque es que de 10
minutes of the video that has to be about
minutos del vídeo que tiene que ir sobre
the company well it is already more than 50%
la empresa pues ya lleva más del 50%
about the relationship no to me
sobre sobre la relación no a mí me suena
this sounds like an ideological discussion that has
esto a discusión ideológica que ha
gone so far that
llegado tan lejos que se han encabezado
one and the other have led the way in being right more
el uno y el otro en tener la razón más
the other than him Maybe Okay then
el otro que él A lo mejor Vale pues
unhappy conal according to him according to him  uh according to
infeliz conal según él según él eh según
him that the person next to him
él de que la persona que tiene al lado
uh is happy and that's not right the
eh sea feliz y eso pues no está bien el
fact is that our relationship was h
caso es que nuestra relación fue h
wearing thin over time
desgastándose a lo largo del tiempo
until this summer this summer well
hasta este verano este verano pues las
things were already quite quite
cosas ya estaban bastante bastante
regular And then e when
regular Y entonces e cuando ya estaba
the summer was almost ending e I contacted
acabando el verano e yo contacté otra
this person again and I said Hey I want to
vez con esta persona y dije Oye to ganas
get back together this summer so we can reach
de volver de verano de que llegemos
agreements so we can be happy again
acuerdos de que volvamos a ser felices
we can be working hard together and I ran into
estemos a tope currando juntos y me topé
this person again like
otra vez con que esta persona como que
my thing my thing my thing my thing my thing and it was
lo mío lo mío lo mío lo mío lo mío y fue
like
como
mm Well the next day Stony my gets
mm Bueno al día siguiente Stony my se
up to look at his phone
levanta a mirar su móvil acción
necessary action on Instagram put your
necesaria en instagram ponga usted su
password and Uy okay here he has skipped
contraseña y Uy vale aquí se ha saltado
a few episodes okay here it gets to that they
unos cuantos episodios vale aquí llega a
were separated they broke up and he
que estaban separados rompieron y él
wanted to be happy with him again
tenía ganas de volver a ser feliz con él
Okay so they gave themselves another chance
Vale entonces se dieron otra oportunidad
but apparently the other one remained in an
pero por lo visto el otro seguía en una
immovable position according to him Until one day he goes to
inamovible Hasta que un día se va a
log into his phone
meter en el móvil
and it appears that he can't enter the
y le aparece que no puede entrar en la
company account that they have
cuenta de la de la empresa que tienen
How strange I didn't enter the password you  I
Qué raro no metí la contraseña te lo
said the [ __ ] he tells me no that I don't know it,
[__] dije me dice que no que no me la sé
like I don't know it kid and I'm like, oh
yo cómo que no me la sé chaval y ya digo
this smells like [ __ ] it turns out my partner
Uy esto huele caca resulta que mi socio
without warning had changed the
sin previo aviso me había cambiado las
passwords of all my
contraseñas de todas las cuentas de
Telop accounts, damn I said, including my
telop [__] dije incluidas mi correo
personal email etc. all my access to
personal etcétera todos mis accesos a
Telop I said had been
telop dije habían sido
revoked, of course This can be
revocados claro Es que esto si se puede
proven, it is a
si se puede demostrar tal cual es un
crime, yes, this can be proven, it
delito
is
si esto se puede demostrar tal cual es
a
un delito
serious crime, both for the business aspect,
importante tanto por el tema de negocio
for the economic aspect, as well as for the
por el tema económico por el como por el
issue of taking away someone's
tema de quitarle a alguien las cuentas
personal accounts. I mean, if you take it, let's go, [ __ ] it,
personales O sea si tú coges vamos te
have balls, piss yourself off, take away
[__] ten [__] te encojones quítale
from your wife or your ex-girlfriend a
a tu a tu mujer o a tu exnovia una
personal account. I mean, no, you can't
cuenta suya personal O sea no no puedes
do
hacer
that, I understand. So, if this can be
eso me enti Entonces si esto loe de
proven, it is a serious crime, I understand,
demostrar es un delito potente entiendo
eh, thank goodness Tesa, thank goodness, daughter. I don't know
eh menos mal tesa menos mal hija No sé
if you're here, thank goodness Tesa, thank goodness,
si estás por aquí menos mal tesa menos
my weapon, you can, daughter, I spoke to him
mal mi arma tú puedes hija hable con él
and he told me that he was out, that he
y me dijo que que estaba fuera que
was out of the project, basically
estaba fuera del proyecto básicamente
that he was kicking me out, how are you going to kick me
que me estaba echando yo cómo me vas a
out if this is from  the two of them and he tells me
echar si esto es de los dos y me dice
This is not from both of us, friend, look, and what does it
Esto no es de los dos amigo mira y qué
teach me? Well, let me tell you
es lo que me enseña Bueno pues os cuento
this summer my partner wanted to do
este verano mi socio quiso hacer de te
it, I said, an SL before we were an SC,
lo [__] dije una sl antes éramos una sc
a civil company What differentiates one from the
una sociedad civil Qué diferencia una de
other, basically the opening costs of
otra básicamente los gastos de apertura
a civil company do not require a
una sociedad civil no es necesario que
notary and it is not necessary to put in
pase por notario y no es necesario meter
an initial capital of 3000 so well
un capital de 3000 inicial entonces
the start is simpler and
bueno el arranque es más sencillo y
since we did not know that I
puesto que no sabíamos que te lo [__]
said I was going to break it, well we decided to
dije iba a reventarlo pues decidimos
do it that way this summer my partner told me to
hacerlo así este verano mi socio me dijo
become an SL and now I look
de convertirnos en sl y ahora lo miro en
back and no, if I'm not mistaken, a
retrospectiva y no si no me equivoco una
s
s
eh, a civil company is a company,
eh una sociedad civil es una sociedad
okay, like any other, but it does not
vale como cualquier otra pero que no
have any businesses, I
tiene negocios no
mean, it does not have
O sea no tiene
income, it's like a company but without
ingresos es como una sociedad pero sin
income, that's why they have to
ingresos Por eso luego la tienen que
transfer it to an
pasar a
SL And then, if that's the case, correct me,
sl Y entonces a mí si es así corregirme
okay, correct me if I'm wrong, but if that
vale corregirme si me equivoco pero si
's the case, a company that is not
es así una sociedad que no está
earning money and then they transfer it to an SL
ingresando y luego la pasan a sl
because they start earning money through
porque empiezan a ganar dinero a través
the
de la de la
account, why because there is a company in the
cuenta por qué porque ha una sociedad a
name of  both of an
nombre de los dos de una cuenta de
Instagram account that is yours or so why do you
Instagram que es tuya o sea para qué
do that it
haces
seems like a coincidence to me But
eso me parece casualidad Pero
coincidentally the day that we had here in
casualmente el día que teníamos aquí en
Madrid the Constitution of the company
Madrid la Constitución de la sociedad
that you have to sign in person before the
que tienes que firmar en persona ante el
notary giving your d and all that stuff Well,
notario dando tu d y todo el rollo Pues
coincidentally, coincidentally, I was in
yo casualmente casualmente estaba en
another country doing one of the few
otro país haciendo uno de los pocos
promotional jobs that I've received
trabajos de promoción que me han llegado
lately So I couldn't be there And
últimamente Así que no podía estar Y
then my partner insisted
entonces mi socio pues me insistió me
insisted and insisted that I had to
insistió y me reinis sió en que yo tenía
leave signed a power of attorney
que dejar firmado un poder notarial
authorizing him to open the sl
autorizando que él pudiese abrir la sl
without me being present Well,
sin que yo estuviese ahí presente Bueno
effectively, as you can
pues yo efectivamente como os podéis
imagine, I signed the said paper with which
imaginar firmé el dicho su papel con el
he himself later and on the day of the
que él mismo después y el día de la
Constitution of the company opened the
Constitución de la sociedad abrió la
new company with 991
nueva sociedad con un 991 de
shares obviously one
participaciones evidentemente el uno de
share for me 99 for him
participaciones para mí el 99 para él
without telling me anything obviously and Uh well I'm getting angry
sin decirme nada obviamente y Eh pues me
Yes but let's see okay he
mecho me Sí pero vamos a ver vale él le
puts 1% to tone and and he gets 99%
pone un 1% a tone y y él se pone un 99%
or in other words he keeps the company the move
o sea se queda la sociedad la movida
here is Uh if this is  can prove
aquí es Eh si esto se puede demostrar
that he deceived you no that he scammed you
que te ha engañado no que te ha estafado
that he used your power your signature
que te ha ha utilizado tu poder tu Firma
to deceive you and such no And you have
para engañarte y tal no Y tienes
conversations where it is proven
conversaciones donde quedan acreditados
that everything was half and half no and that he deceived you
que todo era a medias no y que te engañó
there eh You gave him the power so that he could
ahí eh Tú le diste el poder para que él
put the sl at 5050 of course man yes yes
pusiera el sl al 5050 claro hombre si si
this is demonstrable this can be
esto es demostrable esto se puede se
carried out a major complaint
puede llevar a cabo una una denuncia
no I mean I don't know maybe I'm
no O sea yo no sé a lo mejor estoy
sinning of being innocent or something but I
pecando de inocente o algo pero yo
understand that
entiendo que
this can be reported not sued
esto lo puede denunciar no demandar
David I understand that this is criminal that is what
David Yo entiendo que esto es penal eso
happened audience they have
es lo que ha pasado audience me han
kicked me out of the [ __ ] I said look what they
echado de lo [__] dije mira que me lo
told me Be careful with that kid no
dijeron Ten cuidado con ese chaval no
person I felt that I had to share
persona sentía que tenía que compartir
this with you Audi because it is that
esto con vosotros Audi porque es que
many of you friends and followers
muchos de vosotros amigos y seguidores
eh friends who have told me man I'm going to
eh amigos que me han dicho tío Le voy a
give my sister a sweatshirt of you
regalar a mi hermana una sudadera de te
[ __ ] I said this winter followers
lo [__] dije este invierno seguidores
who have told me Stone these news
que me han dicho Stone estas novidades
we are going to go see you in the store and I as
vamos a ir a verte la tienda y yo como
well they have changed the lock I
pues me han cambiado la cerradura yo ya
no longer have keys to the store Oh
no tengo llaves de la tienda Vaya así
so nothing audience this is basically  what
que nada audience esto es básicamente lo
happened I'm going to do a live stream
que ha pasado voy a hacer un e directo
on Twitch Sure but are you going to do a
en Twitch Claro pero vas a hacer un
live stream on Twitch a video on YouTube and
directo en Twitch un vídeo en YouTube y
no and you're not going to report it inside let's
no lo y no lo vas a denunciar dentro de
see the video when I upload it at 9 Well
a ver el ví cuando lo subo a las 9 Pues
at 10 I'll do a live stream on Twitch
a las 10 haré un directo en Twitch
respond asking the questions that
respond poniendo las preguntas que que
you guys have left pending and nothing to tell you that
os queden pendientes y nada contaros que
well, I'm starting a new
bueno pues estoy Iniciando un nuevo
different project that I'm really
proyecto diferente que me hace mucha
excited about because Well, finally I'm going to be
ilusión porque Bueno pues por fin voy a
able to make all my own decisions and
poder yo tomar todas mis decisiones y
do all the things that I thought were going to
hacer todas las cosas que me parecían
be great projects without anyone
que iban a ser proyectazo sin que nadie
pushing me back because yes and nothing
me los eche atrás porque sí y nada
audience I hope to make videos
audience yo espero volver a hacer vídeos
on YouTube again I have some roommates
en YouTube tengo unos compañeros de piso
who are the best you have to meet I would really like to
que son la [__] tenéis que conocer me
show you this room I think
molaría mucho enseñaros este cuarto que
you're going to love and do a [ __ ]
creo que os va a flipar y hacer un [__]
House tour and do some
House tour y hacer algunas movidas
cool things So nothing audience Thank you for still being
guapas Así que nada audience Gracias por
here after so many [ __ ] years
seguir aquí después de tantos [__] años
thank you for putting up with me Thank you for
gracias por aguantarme Gracias por
supporting me Thank you for
apoyarme Gracias por
Oh there's information that we're missing
Ay hay información que nos falta
Uh there's information that we're missing
Eh hay información que nos falta
eh obviously it's a [ __ ] what they've
eh evidentemente es una putada lo que le
done well it's  it's not that it's a
han hecho bueno es que no es que sea una
[ __ ] it's a crime it would be
putada es que es un delito es que sería
a crime if you can prove it this way it would be
un delito si lo puede demostrar esto así
a crime but of
sería un delito pero
course we'll have to wait because it wouldn't
claro habrá que esperar porque no me
surprise me if the other guy
extrañaría que el otro se
speaks out what can I say dude I mean eh
pronuncias qué te digo tío o sea eh
and you upload a video come on then I'm going to
y subes un vídeo no venga pues voy a
do another project to suck off the guy who
hacer otro proyecto a chuparle al que me
took away from me I wouldn't let them
han quitado yo no me dejaría que me
take something like that from me because if not that
quitaran una cosa así porque si tampoco
easy and I'm never going to fight for
no así de fácil y no peleo nunca más por
it again no me eh I personally don't know how
ella no yo eh yo personalmente no sé
tell me what you
decirme qué
think
opináis
Well let's see some other stuff
Bueno vamos a ver alguna otra cosilla
no Ricky Ed uploaded a video today
no Ricky Ed ha subido hoy un vídeo
dude the truth is the thumbnail is
tío la verdad es que la miniatura está
nice dude I mean the truth is the
guapa tío O sea la verdad es que la
thumbnail is nice dude and it also
miniatura está guapa tío y además es que
has like a filter as if it was him
tiene como un filtro como si fuera él
drawn and he doesn't give a damn and he puts on he
dibujado y y se la suda y se pone se
puts on horns in the thumbnail okay But
pone cuern él en la miniatura vale Pero
if you look at the profile picture and such of the
si veis la foto de perfil y tal de la
girl it's
chica es
a It's about the subject of the puff babe I'm
un Es sobre el tema del puff nene lo
sorry Yeah okay I mean about
siento Sí vale o sea sobre sobre la
orlock's lover let's see what Ricky
orlock vamos a ver qué ha dicho Ricky
Eddie said already We were more or less watching and
Eddie ya Estuvimos viendo más o menos y
commenting on what  She said
comentando lo que dijo
on Twitter but let's see
en en Twitter pero vamos a ver más
her opinion in more detail on video that
extensamente su opinión en vídeo que a
maybe expresses itself better and we have
lo mejor se expresa mejor y lo hemos
understood it wrong you know because
entendido nosotros mal lo sabes porque
the girl says deep down I know that you only
la chavala dice en el fondo sé que solo
want to support, I mean when you already know that
quieres apoyar o sea cuando ya sabes que
the guy wants that and you have a
el tío lo que quiere es eso Y tienes
partner, well no because she's single the
pareja que bueno no porque está soltera
guy is talking to her like a couple, he
tío le está hablando como una pareja le
told her that they are going to live together that he
ha dicho que se van a vivir juntos que
will show her that he can create a
le va a demostrar que puede crear una
person and that it doesn't have to hurt I don't know
persona y que no tiene que doler no sé
what couples are, they are boyfriends or at least they
qué son parejas son novios o al menos se
are treating each other as such well no no no no
están tratando como tal mismo
here I don't
bueno no no no no aquí no estoy de
agree with this you know that the guy
acuerdo en esto ya sabes que el tío lo
wants that and you have a partner,
que quiere es eso Y tienes pareja que
well no because she's single the guy is
bueno no porque está soltera tío le está
talking to her like a couple, he told her that they are
hablando como una pareja le ha dicho que
going to live together that he will
se van a vivir juntos que le va a
show her that he can create a person and
demostrar que puede crear una persona y
that it doesn't have to hurt I don't know what
que no tiene que doler no sé qué son
couples are, they are not a couple, they are almost something I mean they are
parejas son no son parej son casi algo O
not a couple, they have
sea no son pareja tienen
something, they have something okay
algo tienen algo vale
eh if they were a couple, she
eh si fueran pareja ella
eh Let's see
eh A ver
if they were a couple
si si fueran pareja
eh It's that I think that they hadn't even
eh Es que yo creo que incluso ni se
seen each other in person, she
habían visto en persona esto alne lo
said this and she was the one who fell for it and me
decía y fue ella la que cayó y yo
too  I realized that it's like it's true it's
también caí en eso es como es verdad es
true I think they haven't seen each other
verdad creo que no se han llegado a ver
in person it's like it's a person
en persona es como que es una persona
with whom she has been chatting for a while blah
con la que lleva tiempo Charlando bla
blah blah blah blah but there's nothing in
bla bla bla bla bla pero no hay nada en
the conversation if you realize that
la conversación si te das cuenta que te
indicates that they have seen each other in
indique que se han visto en
person she has her boyfriend Javi on chat Oh
persona ella le novio Javi por chat Ay
really but it's called a second in
de verdad pero se lo llama un segundo en
a context that you say You know but
un contexto de que tú dices Sabes pero
no It's that I think they haven't
que no Es que creo que no se han visto
even seen each other in
ni en
person that I think they haven't even seen each other
persona que creo que no se han visto ni
in
en
person my boyfriend is you that's like
persona mi novio eres tú eso es como
something that she says let's see me more than
algo que se dice ella a ver yo más que
a boyfriend more than a couple okay I see
un novio más que una pareja vale Yo veo
that she gets the
que ella le hace ilusiones al
boy excited I see that she gets the
chico yo veo que ella le hace ilusiones
boy excited But it's not
al chico Pero no es
Eh it's not
Eh no es
true it's not even friends with benefits Rob
verdad es que ni amigos con derecho Rob
It's that what part of the
Es que qué parte de la
conversation what part of the
conversación qué parte de la
conversation shows you that they have even
conversación te demuestra que se han
seen each other in person
visto en persona
is that I think they have not
siquera es que yo creo que no se han
even seen each other in person I think it's a
visto ni en persona yo creo que es un
twitterer and a twitterer of these that
twittero y una twittera de estos que
are in all the rolls behind the
están en todos los rollos detrás de los
youtubers I don't know what I don't know how much and And those
youtubers no sé qué no sé cuánto y Y esa
people don't and  and they meet they start
gente no y y se conocen empiezan a
talking and they talk eh And and it's
hablar y se hablan eh Y y es
virtual Minerva says let's see on more than one
virtual dice Minerva a ver en más de una
occasion some guy introduced me as his
ocasión algún chico me presentó como su
girlfriend and nothing to do with it and Mika says I've
novia y nada que ver y dice Mika yo he
had several of those boyfriends many are not that it's
tenido varios de esos novios muchos no
a way of speaking at that
son que es una forma de hablar en ese
moment in which the guy is
momento en el que el chico está
worried and she says to him Don't worry
preocupado y ella le dice Tú tranquilo
that I didn't see you it's you but what is that I
que m no viio eres tú pero que es que
think they haven't seen each other in
creo que no se han visto en
person I mean what part of the
persona O sea qué qué parte de la
conversation confirms to you that they have
conversación os confirma a ustedes que
seen each other in person even if they are
se han visto en persona aunque sea son
boyfriends at least they are treating each other as
novios al menos se están tratando como
such the same guy has described it as
tal el mismo chaval lo ha descrito como
a [ __ ] marriage Okay when you know that
un [__] matrimonio Vale cuando sabes eso
for no The guy doesn't describe it as a
por no El chaval no lo describe como un
[ __ ] marriage he says an almost something my
[__] matrimonio dice un casi algo mi
almost something I'll tell you the story of How
casi algo os cuento la historia de Cómo
my almost something goes with
mi casi algo se va con
oslo you keep talking to a person
oslo sigues hablando con una persona
when you already have clear their intentions
cuando ya tienes claras sus intenciones
what the [ __ ] and I feel stupid because
qué [__] y me siento tonta porque
everyone tells me so gosh all your
todos me lo dicen vaya todas tus señales
close signals all your trusted people
cercanas todas tus personas de confianza
told you that the guy Maybe he
te decían que el chaval A lo mejor
only wanted to flirt with you no no
solamente quería ofar con lleva no no
but it doesn't matter what
pero si es que da igual que se lo digan
the people around him tell him if  that she she
las personas alrededor si que ella ella
knew for weeks Well I don't know how much
lo sabía semanas Bueno no sé cuánto
time has passed since the last message
tiempo de mensaje ha pasado en todo este
but she's been talking to
tiempo pero lleva semanas hablando con
a guy for weeks who knows he wants to sleep with her
un pibe que sabe que se la quiere tirar
and he hasn't told her he has a boyfriend so
y no le ha dicho que tiene novio por lo
if the guy is interested in
tanto si el tío tiene interés en
sleeping with her and the girl doesn't post anything
tirársela y la chavala no publica nada
with him and doesn't tell him she has a partner
con él y no le dice que tiene pareja
Well if the other guy or what she likes he's going to
Pues si al otro al or lo que le gusta se
want to break it as is normal
la va a querer reventar como es normal
that it will end up
que acabe
happening of course I know but also she
pasando claro se pero es que además ella
plays man there was a thread there was a thread
juega tío había un hilo había un hilo
that had me doing somersaults at 7 in
que me tuvo dando volteretas a las 7 de
the morning and I'm going to take advantage of Ricky's video
la mañana y voy a aprovechar el vídeo de
to read it man I'm going to read it
Ricky para leerlo tío lo voy a leer
quickly because we're going to
rápido porque vamos
uh I'm going to put it up quickly and I'm going to read it
eh lo voy a poner rápido y lo voy a leer
quickly okay because I don't
rápido por encima vale porque no me
want to focus on the guy but on
quiero centrar en el ilo sino en
him in Ricky's video to see what he
el en el vídeo del Ricky para ver qué lo
thinks but look look at
que opina pero es
me explaining Why you shouldn't be that
yo explicando Por qué no debe ser ese
constructed Ally that they ask you
Aliado de construido que ellas te piden
for to manipulate you and take advantage of you
para manipularte y aprovecharse de ti
okay
vale
look at a constructed and not at all
mira un chavalín de construido y nada
toxic kid excited about his girlfriend
tóxico ilusionado con su novia pone a
tests his limits watching  how she stays
prueba su límite viendo cóm ella queda
with a turn fete until what we
con un fete de turn hasta que pasa lo
all knew happens damn with the new
que todos sabíamos cuerno con las nuevas
currents of modern feminism we have
corrientes del feminismo moderno hemos
seen many times words like you have to
visto muchas veces palabras como tienes
deconstruct your masculinity he is just
que deconstruir tu masculinidad es solo
a friend don't be toxic sleeping
un amigo no seas tóxico que duerma
naked with a friend in bed does not
desnuda con un amigo en la cama no
mean anything I have always greeted him
significa nada yo siempre lo he saludado
with a kiss and so on the friend here was
con un beso y demás la amiga aquí fue
very smart she knows that the boy is young and
muy lista sabe que el chaval es joven e
inexperienced we have verified it because already
inexperto lo hemos comprobado porque ya
uh the boy uploaded photos of himself to his
eh el chico subió fotos de él a su
Twitter and he is a he is a kid I mean I think he is I think he is
Twitter y es un es un crío o sea yo creo
younger than her
que es Yo creo que es más joven que ella
The boy uh the vixen knows how to give him a
El chaval eh la arpía sabe cómo darle en
lift so that he believes that she is
su corazoncito para que él crea que
worth it and that she is a
merezca la pena y que es una chica
wonderful girl spoiler it is not she
maravillosa spoiler no lo es ella
starts to meet orlock boy in the
empieza a conocer a orlock chaval de la
photo typical modern pseudo influencer
foto típico pseudo influencer moderno
but since it is Lita she does not want to let go of her
pero como es Lita no quiere soltar a su
provider man without first making sure of the
hombre proveedor sin antes asegurarse el
result this does
resultado esto
not want to let go of her provider man
no quiere soltar a su hombre proveedor
without first making sure of the result we
sin antes asegurarse el resultado esto
also saw this where uh where
lo vimos también donde eh donde
Ricky where Ricky and Lali we also saw it
Ricky donde Ricky y Lali lo vimos
okay
también vale
because one thing that one thing is that  you
porque una cosa que una una cosa es que
lose your head one day You're
se te vaya la cabeza un día Estás
drunk okay you're not good with your partner
borracha vale estás mal con tu pareja
okay you're not good and on top of that someone comes along that
vale estás mal y encima te viene alguien
you're attracted to well no no but the thing is that
que te atrae bueno no no pero es que
Lali is
Lali
not only sleeping with that guy
no solamente se acuesta con el chico ese
but she's also pulling strings to
sino que ella está moviendo hilo para
plan another get together okay let's see if she
planear otra quedada vale a ver si lo
hooks him and she doesn't leave Ricky because she
engancha y no deja a Ricky porque al
doesn't hook the other one with Ricky she acts like
otro no lo engancha con Ricky actúa como
nothing happened and convinces and
si no hubiera pasado nada y convence y
mobilizes her entire group so that Ricky never finds
moviliza todo su grupo para que nunca se
out at
entere
that age a lot of
Ricky con esas edades se cometen muchos
mistakes are made I said it the other day it could be
errores yo lo dije el otro día puede ser
perfectly possible that you
perfectamente que tú le pongas los
cheat on your partner but the next morning you
cuernos a tu pareja pero a la mañana
leave him you understand But this is a
dejes me entiendes Pero esto es un
movement to make sure someone
movimiento de que asegurarte a alguien
okay look that's why she uses the tricks of having female
vale mira por eso usa las argucias de ha
iq it's very ugly so that her boyfriend
iq femal es muy feo para que su novio
Cook doesn't feel
Cook no se sienta
threatened the limits of the
amenazado los límites de la
deconstruction of masculinity of the
deconstrucción de masculinidad del
boy begin to falter it doesn't
chaval empiezan a tambalearse no le hace
even sting him and he claims something he smells but the
ni picaa y reclama algo se huele pero la
female showing greater iq than the male
hembra mostrando mayor iq que el macho
tells him that although she knows that he only wants to
le dice que aunque sabe que solo quiere
put the poison in her he hasn't yet
meterle la venenosa aún no le ha
insinuated nothing, so she says this
insinuado nada o sea esto lo dice ella
in the conversation So she knows that
en la conversación O sea ella sabe que
the other guy wants to [ __ ] okay but he has
el otro lo que quiere [__] vale pero
n't told her anything that they have been
que no le ha dicho nada que han han
talking about video games and
estado hablando de videojuegos y de
music videos and
videoclips y de
tattoos how do you know that he wants to [ __ ] you
tatuajes cómo sabes que te quiere [__]
okay something something has fallen on you know what I mean it is known it is known there is
vale algo algo te ha caído me entiendes
no need for me to
se sabe se sabe no hace falta que te lo
tell you explicitly the moment arrives the
diga explícitamente llega el momento el
goring bull shows interest in the
toro corneador muestra interés por la
girl and she showing off her
mosa y ella haciendo gala de su
intelligence decides to
inteligencia decide
tell him the mind game with
contárselo empieza el juego mental con
her boyfriend begins and the psychological torture I don't know
su novio y la tortura psicológica no sé
if I should say yes to test her
si decirle que sí para tantear los celo
heat the result is lethal for
de heche el resultado es letal para
him
él
eh of
eh
course The most logical thing here is for
claro Es que aquí lo más Lógico es que
you to tell him do you want to do with a guy
tú le digas quieres que ha con un tío
tell him to be a guy who wants to
decirle que sea un tío que te quiere
[ __ ] you if you meet up with him well we
[__] si quedas con él pues nosotros ya
won't see each other anymore kiss
no nos vemos más un beso
Pilar The M tries to compete with the other
Pilar El M intenta competir con el otro
male saying that he is inviting you to his house he
macho diciendo que é invita a su casa
fails miserably she first
falla estrepitosamente ella primero le
tells him that if they meet up he can go and
dice que si quedan él puede ir y se lo
introduces him but he gives her away Then he says that he is
presenta pero la delata Luego decir que
not clear okay he doesn't know
él no tiene claro vale que él no sabe
that she has a boyfriend okay look how cute  my
que tiene novio vale mira qué mono mi
love Well look, if one day you come
amor Pues mira ya si un día vienes
with me I'll tell him to stay Okay so that way you'll
conmigo le digo de quedar Vale pues así
get to know him love haha I'll introduce you and that's
lo conoces amor jaja te lo presento y es
how I introduce you and all And now later on
como te lo presento y tal Y ahora luego
he says he knows about my existence and she
dice él sabe de mi existencia y ella le
says well not yet love but if I meet up with
dice pues aún no amor pero si quedo con
him you'll see that I'll drop the bomb on him you know She's
él ya verás tú que le suelto la bomba
playing with him she's playing
sabes Se lo va jugando con él va jugando
with him you know you'll see that I'll drop the bomb there you have
con é sabes verás tú que le suelto ahí
n't told him you haven't told him you
la no se la has contado no se la has
know anyway total The Movida
contado sabes en fin total La Movida
eh
eh
anyway here comes the part where he actually
en fin aquí viene la parte en la que ya
tells him Of course but it's that Oh it's
se lo dice Claro pero es que Oh es que
that thread this thread this thread it's to me that
ese hilo este hilo este hilo me es que
thread was for another excerpt dude and I
ese hilo era para otro extracto tío y lo
left it I left it and I didn't I didn't comment on it But oh well
dejé lo dejé y no lo no lo comenté Pero
How It's logical kid what is this
bueno Cómo Es lógico chaval qué es esto
I know that maybe you're really young that you
yo sé que a lo mejor eres muy crío que
're not aware of what it means when
no eres consciente de lo que significa
your girlfriend tells you that she knows that a
que tu novia te diga que sabe que un
guy is talking to her
chaval le está hablando única
exclusively to play her But it seems to you that it's
exclusivamente para jugársela Pero a ti
not and that everything is a world
te parece que no y que todo es un mundo
of wonder and color that's Okay it's that
de maravilla y de color eso está Okay es
[ __ ] it up I've been through me that
que [__] yo pasado por mí que se ciñen
the moves that we are going to read below are pretty much limited
bastante las movidas que vamos a leer a
But at no time did I
continuación Pero en ningún momento
get to read this [ __ ] [ __ ] at
llego a leer esta [__] [__] en un
first I got to have this context
principio llego a tener este contexto
this information at first and from the
esta información en un principio y de
start I already do
entrada ya hago
this outward door What are you doing there wrong
así puerta para fuera Qué haces ahí mal
says the one who is not
dice el que no tiene nada de
wrong let's see It's that you say
malo a ver Es que es que que digas tú
That if you had this context you already
Que si llegas a tener este contexto ya
tell her the door but if you caught her
le dices puerta pero si la pillaste ya
after having done it
después de haberlo hecho
and you defended the lie that she had been
y le defendiste la [__] de que la
raped that nobody who has
violado que eso no se lo cree nadie que
a little knowledge on the
tenga un poquito de conocimiento en la
subject will believe that you
materia
know
sabes
man, I mean if you have this context
hombre o sea si tú tienes este contexto
that they want to stay you give her the door But
de que quieren quedar le das puerta Pero
if you already find out that she
si ya te enteras de que ella se la
[ __ ] her if she tells you that it was I mean you
follado si ella te dice que ha sido O
're seeing conversations and such you
sea estás viendo conversaciones y tal te
find out through investigations not
enteras por por investigaciones no
because she
porque te lo
tells you but you defend that there was a
cuenta pero defiendes que que había una
rape love then I feel bad
violación amor entonces me siento mal
because I don't want you to be bad either and
porque tampoco quiero que tú estés mal y
says love that you're doing everything right well
dice amor que lo estás haciendo todo
everything everything except the part about being
bien bueno todo todo excepto lo de ser
a [ __ ] The rest goes there for forward
una [__] Lo demás va ahí para adante
as long as he doesn't get too close to you You know I
mientras no se te acerque mucho Sabes
have nothing in  against any
que no tengo nada en contra de ningún
man have a great time and she says if she
hombre pásatelo genial y dice ella si
just approached me to say hello and
solo se me ha acercado para saludarme y
goodbye [ __ ] That after or before I
despedirse [__] Eso después o antes de
put you on all fours your boyfriend is
que te pusiera a cuatro tu novio te está
telling you that he's anxious I don't know man that you
diciendo que está con ansiedad no sé tío
're so anxious that you're
que te estás tando ansiedad que que
insecure that you don't like the plan
estás inseguro que no te gusta el plan
how is she supposed to be your girlfriend and no he doesn't
qué tal se supone que es tu novia y no
respect you or an insecurity that
no te respeta ni una inseguridad que
is completely justified you know you see Ali
está completamente justificada sabes ves
poor kid How innocent how
Alí pobre chaval Qué inocente que
innocent no how hick dude he's very cool that I
inocente no que palurdo tío es muy primo
'm not insulting bad you're
que no estoy insultando malas de eres
stupid that I don't know he's not a battery Brody
tonto que no sé que no es un pila Brody
is a battery he tells him The kid and this What is it I do
es pila le dice El chaval y esto Qué es
n't understand anything learn from this
no entiendo nada de aprende de esta
learn eh that's life dude that's life
aprende eh es la vida tío es la vida
Look it's quite
Mira es bastante
probable or not No Not necessarily but
probable o no No No necesariamente pero
man the girl is seen Hey
hombre a la chica sí que se la ve Oye
what do you think the influencers who say you don't
qué piensas los influencers que dicen no
know me to throw tremendous
me conoces para aventarse tremendas
gadas if what we know is what they
gadas si lo que conocemos es lo que
show son that will depend on the context
muestran hijo que dependerá del contexto
not on what you're telling me
no de lo que me estés diciendo
[Music] look Maybe
[Música]
she I don't know if for sure
que mira A lo mejor ella no sé si seguro
but she sees her Pilar at the time  to act Maybe it's like that
pero se la ve Pilar a la hora de actuar
eh And that's it but maybe
A lo mejor es así eh Y ya está pero a lo
she's suffered things similar to what
ella pues ha sufrido cosas parecidas a
she's doing now you
la que ella está haciendo ahora me
know what I mean maybe she's found
entiendes a lo mejor ella ha dado con
someone dude always always
alguien tío siempre siempre
eh I don't know if that's still the case or
eh yo no sé si si eso sigue siendo así o
not but when I was a kid
no pero cuando yo era chaval
when a guy was good to a
con cuando un chico era bueno con una
girl okay And he wanted to be good and behave
chica vale Y quería ser bueno y portarse
and such he'd give it to you he'd give it to you at the
bien y tal te daba te la daba a la
entrance at the exit from the sides he'd
entrada a la salida por los lados te la
give it to you from all sides but nevertheless yes yes yes it
daba por todos lados pero sin embargo si
was ota yes if you let her [ __ ] without
si si era ota si si la dejabas tirar sin
warning if he didn't call yes I don't know what I don't know
avisar si no llamaba si no sé qué no sé
how much Or
cuánto O
rather she they kind of gave themselves
sea ella ellas como que se entregaban
more no So it's quite likely that it's
más no Entonces es bastante probable que
happened to her before
a ella eh le haya pasado anteriormente
with some guy or whatever because she got
con algún chaval o lo que sea porque que
caught by some [ __ ] who ignored
le haya cogido un cabrón que pasara de
her who spoke badly to her or who
ella que le hablara mal o que
just let her [ __ ] and things like that you
directamente la dejara tirar y cosas de
know And then she grabs
esas sabes Y entonces ella coge al chico
this guy from Twitter not this joker and and he's
este del Twitter no al joro este y y es
a sweetie and she goes and goes She
un caramelo y lo va y lo va Lo va
molds him and also eh she tells him how to
moldeando además eh le va diciendo cómo
think how to act I mean she
tiene que pensar có tiene que actuar o
tells him everything  Look how she
sea le va diciendo todo Fíjate cómo le
tells him Look how she tells him eh how she
dice Fíjate cómo le dice eh cómo lo
does it so that the boy has normalized
hace para que el chico tenga normalizado
in their relationship that she gives while she gets
en su relación que ella de mientras va
to know him and not complain
conociendo al orlo y que no te quejes
that if you are not toxic eh you are
que si no eres un tóxico eh lo estás
doing very well You are a very
haciendo muy bien Eres un hombre muy
deconstructed man nothing after I say that I don't know
deconstruido nada despes digo que no sé
says I'm going to leave home for a while no that
dice me voy a ir de casa un rato no ese
boy is not going to believe in feminism
chico ya no va a creer más en el femin
itself anymore or in deconstructions or any
mismo ni en las deconstrucciones ni
of that [ __ ] for the next time
[__] de esas para la próxima que le
someone comes to tell him how you are
venga alguien a decirle tú cómo eres
you are deconstructed and he's going to say look at the
eres deconstruido y va a decir mira el
Lego the Lego of Jai's mini that you
Lego el Lego de la mini de la Jai que la
have had under the table for a year well that's
tenéis debajo la mesa hace un año pues
how I am deconstructed I'll hold on any longer he
así estoy de de construido aguanto más
says maybe I'll see him again and it will happen
dice puede que lo vea otra vez y pase de
again I suppose she basically tells him
nuevo Supongo le dice ella básicamente
the girl so that we understand each other has
la tía para que nos entendamos le ha
sent him this message Not because she feels
mandado este mensaje No porque se sienta
bad because the guy is very good and she
mal porque el chaval es muy bueno y ella
has slept with another one who is also good but
se ha tirado a otro que también sino
because she thought about seeing me a
porque ha pensado a ver me fado un
famous person or someone who turns me on more or
famoso o alguien que me pone más o lo
whatever that I like her thing or
que sea que me gusta su rollo o lo que
whatever having a boyfriend me  I want to throw him back out
sea teniendo novio me lo quiero volver a
but I don't want to lose what I have
tirar pero no quiero perder lo que tengo
with my current partner because I guess he
con mi actual pareja porque Supongo que
loves me he shows it to me he takes care of me he
me quiere me lo demuestra me cuida me
gives me gifts he is with me until
hace regalo está conmigo hasta tiempo
such time So I'm going to tell him that I
tal Entonces le voy a contar que me he
slept with the other guy and maybe since he
tirado al otro y a lo mejor como me
loves me so much he will tell me that he understands that
quiere tanto me dice que lo entiende que
we are good but I can continue with the
estamos bien pero yo puedo seguir con el
other guy because I want to sleep with him because I like him
otro porque me lo quiero tirar porque me
because I'm that dirty no and that's it to me it seems
Mola porque soy así de cerda no y ya
that way Because no
mensaje va de esa manera Por no
man it would
hombre me
seem to me it would seem too much I
parecería me parecería demasiado Yo
understand that it's a
entiendo que es un mensaje de
farewell message to me it would seem no no chat what do you
despedida me parecería no no chat
think I mean it would seem to me
ustedes qué pensáis O sea me parecería
already let's go a hard face like er
ya una vamos una cara dura como er
diamond
diamante
eh that I send him that message with the
eh que que le mande ese mensaje con la
intention that he settles not like
intención de que él se conforme no en
hold on because I'm going to be
plan aguanta que me lo voy a estar
sleeping with him and then you if that a kiss
tirando y ya luego tú si eso un beso
trianero Thank you very much for that
trianero Muchas gracias por ese
gift with what Papo anything you
regalo con qué Papo cualquier cosa
have underneath you identify yourself you sit
tengas debajo te identifiques te sientas
down today you let him go maybe I'll see him again
hoy le sueltas puede que lo vea otra vez
and it will happen again I suppose the
y pase de nuevo Supongo le dice el
guy says will you block him for me like it's that
chaval lo bloquearas por mí en plan de
you've gone to a guy who  qua
es que te has fado un tío que me qua
insecure and such well Ah precisely that in
insegura y tal bueno Ah precisamente que
addition you have [ __ ] him you have
además te lo has follado me lo has
confessed to me she tells him I can't do
confesado le dice ella no puedo hacer
that Sorry Yeah yeah he tells her I would
eso Perdón Sí sí él le dice lo
block him for me I mean without her it's that of
bloquearía por mí o sea él sin que ella
course here I don't see him the same as
es que claro aquí yo no lo veo igual que
Ricky I mean she doesn't send him the message
Ricky O sea ella no le manda el mensaje
like This is what it is But I'm still
en plan Esto es lo que hay Pero sigo
with you no no no no she sends him the
contigo no no no no ella le manda el
message like This is what it is and
mensaje en plan Esto es lo que hay y
here I stay and I'm going to do it again
aquí me quedo y lo voy a volver hac esta
tonight okay don't count on me yaam
noche vale que no cuentes conmigo yaam
more than I don't know worrying about the [ __ ]
más que no me se agobiando con el [__]
phone all night again
móvil toda la noche otra
but he without her asking him he
vez pero él sin que ella se lo pida él
's Opening doors to forgive her it's
está Abriendo puertas para perdonarla es
like that Cook he Opens doors I would
así de Cook él Abre puertas lo
block him for me I mean after what after after he has
bloquearía por mí o sea después de lo
done it
que después después de que la ha hecho
after after he has done it he
después de después de que la ha hecho él
tells her I would block him for me hoping
le dice lo bloquearía por mí esperando
that she says Sure yes my love I'll
que ella diga Claro que sí mi amor me lo
sleep with him last and block him Okay and I'll
tiro la última y lo bloqueo Vale y
go back
vuelvo
with you until there I can't get there I'm sorry no no
contigo hasta ahí No llego lo siento no
this You're asking me it's going away
no esto Me estás pidiendo se me va se me
the world is going away from me anyway Baby I don't think  go
va el mundo en fin Nene no pienso entrar
into detail I'm not stupid that's going to be
en detalle no estoy tonta eso va a ser
worse She says But there's been something else help
peor Dice Pero ha habido algo más ayuda
something more than that they brush her friend
algo más de que se la cepillen amigo
she says How can something be clearer if I already
dice ella Cómo que algo más claro si ya
made it clear to you that things have happened that
te dejo claro que han pasado cosas que
have blown me up
me ha reventado dice ayúdame habéis
she says help me baby I'm
pollado le dice ella ayúdame nene lo
sorry Yes gentlemen I baby I'm sorry
siento Sí señores yo le nene lo siento
Yes and pu Tena like a joke anyway Pass
Sí y pu Tena como una broma en fin Pasa
this thread and I read it I go
este hilo y yo lo leo me vuelvo
absolutely crazy and I can't help it
absolutamente loco y no puedo evitar
[ __ ] This is not what I was going to
[__] Esto no es lo que yo iba a
comment but here we have it to delete
comentar pero aquí lo tenemos pal quitar
the tweet and comment the following your
el twet y comentar lo siguiente tu
ex-girlfriend is a [ __ ] filthy piece of [ __ ]
exnovia es una [__] [__] de [__] sin
worthless and you are a loser you piece of [ __ ] wake up
valor y tú un pringaos hoja de [__]
and move on believe me I know what I'm
espabila y avanza créeme sé de lo que
talking about clearly this tweet unleashes a stir
hablo claro este tweet desata un revuelo
that shits everyone starts
que te cagas todo el mundo empieza a
commenting on it everyone on
comentarlo lo citan toda la gente de
Twitter football quotes it feminists
Twitter fúbol lo citan la feministas lo
quotes it feminists quotes it
citan los feministos lo citan las
feminists everyone quotes it
feministes todo el mundo lo cita
saying But what are you going to talk if they were
diciendo Pero tú qué vas a hablar si a
you  hell I don't know what
ti te fueron infier no sé qué
exactly friends precisely I already
precisamente amigues precisamente yo ya
went through what need to discover it in
pasé por lo que necesidad descubrirla de
the worst possible way which was on my
la peor manera posible que fue por mi
own without anyone confessing it to me
propia cuenta sin que me lo confesaran
I had to find it which is quite a thing
tuve yo que encontrarlo que vaya telita
and I know what it means and what it means to
y sé lo que significa y lo que supone
interpret the signs to this day
interpretar las señales al día de hoy
unfortunately at the time I didn't have
por desgracia yo en la época no tuve
those signs because when I was aware
esas señales porque cuando estaba al
of the plans they had they
tanto de los planes que tenían siempre
were always in relation to friends and
eran relación a amigas y personas de
trusted people that I myself knew,
confianza que yo mismo conocía a las que
some of which I even cared for Because they were
alguna incluso tenía cariño Porque eran
trustworthy people for me and for
personas de confianza para mí y para
perjan at that time But this
perjan en aquel entonces Pero esto le
happened to this guy in signs your
pasado este Chaval en señales de tu
girlfriend is saying I'm talking to
novia está diciendo estoy hablando con
a guy that you want to [ __ ] me she told me to
un tío que me quieres [__] me ha dicho
go to her house I'm going to go you
que me vaya a su casa voy a ir me has
told me that you believed I was safe I'm going you
dicho que te cre seguridad voy a ir me
told me that you had a bad time because I'm
has dicho que lo has pasado mal porque
going she's at her house I'm going back I've
voy est en su casa voy a volver me lo he
done it but I want to continue okay eh there are
fado pero quiero seguir vale Eh hay
differences in the case the other day I
diferencias en el caso el otro día os
was telling you that I saw that the
estuve comentando que yo veía que los
cases were incomparable and here Ricky
casos eran incomparables y aquí Ricky
is putting other differences okay
está poniendo otras diferencias vale Yo
For example I put differences eh between the
por ejemplo puse diferencias eh entre el
case of Ali and this girl in which the
caso de Ali y esta chica en la que la
This girl behaved better than Lali
chica esta se comportaba mejor que Lali
in the sense that the next day she
en el sentido de que al día siguiente se
tells her and makes it clear that she's going to do it
lo cuenta y le deja claro que lo va a
again and such and here Ricky is
volver a hacer y tal y aquí Ricky está
making other comparisons not other
poniendo otras comparaciones no otras
differences in which it is easier for him to
diferencias en la que para él es más
trust her and give it to you
fácil confiar en ella y que te la dé Por
Why Because she stayed with this guy But she
qué Porque l quedaba con este chico Pero
always did it through groups of
lo hacía siempre a través de grupos de
friends that were trustworthy already in the
amigos que eran de confianza ya en la
couple no I mean there was no
pareja no O sea que no había
problem Yes also of course they are
problema Sí también claro es que son
different stories and already I mean no no no
historias diferent y ya O sea no no no
no everything that is horns from a girl
no todo lo que sea cuernos de una chica
with a snake tattoo is the same let's
con tatuaje de serpiente es lo mismo a
see yes it is true that there are some
ver sí que es verdad que hay algunos
patterns that you say you watch out watch out that you already
patrones que dices tú ojito ojito que ya
know but already the story each one is
me sabes pero ya la historia cada uno es
different one sear better another worse another you
diferente una sear mejor otra peor otro
know with you do you care if I
sabes contigo te importa si me vuelvo a
support you again it's disgusting this is disgusting
apoyar es asqueroso esto es asqueroso
this should have realized it already
esto para haberse dado cuenta hace ya
but well then I put this that is a
pero bueno entonces pongo esto que es un
TT the truth is quite harsh I already tell you
TT la verdad bastante duro ya os digo
without any intention of offending the kid
sin ninguna intención de ofender al pibe
because this is simply child is
porque esto es simplemente niño es
spica go ahead I know he is a
espila tira para adelante sé que es un
kid but it is that what it touches  now it's time to
crío pero es que lo que toca ahora toca
eat your [ __ ] and move forward
comerte los h teón y tirar para adante
like it's happened to us before and
como nos ha pasado alguna vez y para
forward and people like that came in What
adante y entraron gente como na Que me
the guy told me, he has completely trusted
dijo el chaval ha confiado plenamente en
his partner and there seemed to be good
su pareja y parecía haber buena
communication well on his part the
comunicación bueno por parte de él la
guy doesn't tell him anything for two days
chaval no le cuenta nada los dos días
because she feels like a [ __ ] and at the
porque se siente una zorra y al fin al
end of the day she [ __ ] up her crucial definition in a
cabo se cña su definición crucial en una
healthy relationship if it turns out that she was
relación sana si resulta que ella
hiding things it's not the guy's fault he
ocultaba cosas no es culpa del chaval
should have banned her from hanging out with her
debería haberle prohibido quedar con sus
friends it's a complicated subject for
amigos es un tema complicado para
anyone I tell you I see a
cualquier persona le digo yo a veo un
gigantic margin between being trusting AND
margen gigantesco entre ser confiado Y
being too innocent If your partner has been
ser demasiado inocente Si tu pareja
telling you for weeks that she's going along with
lleva semana diciendote que le sigue el
a guy she doesn't know that
rollo a un tío que no conoce que todo el
everyone has said so that she wants to sleep with her
mundo lo ha dicho que se la quiere tirar
and despite you telling her it makes you
y pesa a que tú le digas que te crea
insecure She had to stop
inseguridad Ella tenía que dejar de
talking to him that way he started to
hablar con él de esa forma la comenza
stop her to her city and go to sleep at
parer a su ciudad y se vaya a dormir a
her house and throughout the whole process you instead of
su casa y en todo el proceso tú en vez
saying Yes man What are you going to do
decirle Sí hombre Tú de qué vas la an
continue like that Well yes I
seguir adelante de esa forma Pues sí
think I'll be screwing you no matter how much you
creo que te estaré empanado por mucho
love her and respect her you're
que la quieras y la respetas tienes
right there were signs and she  he stretched
razón habían señales y ella tensó
the rope too much but I do not agree that
demasiado la cuerda pero no comparto que
he is the one who is breaded I am sorry but I
él sea el empanado Lo siento pero lo
think so Full trust is the greatest
opino t La confianza plena es el mayor
pillar in a relationship I totally
Pilar en una relación Estoy totalmente
agree but as there are signs that
de acuerd pero como tiene señales que
are so evident that any
son tan evidentes que cualquier ser
neuronal being even belonging to one end is
neuronal incluso perteneciendo a una end
quite more lights the way I think I
bastante más luces la manera que creo Le
forgive him almost everything
perdono casi todo
Haha What does Jorge say realize that it is a
Jaja Qué dice Jorge cuenta de que es un
danger and a risk well anyway and do not
peligro y un riesgo pues en fin y no
say no but it is that the looks of the
digáis no pero es que las pintas de las
girls that I do not know what too the looks of
chavalas que no sé qué too las pintas de
a person no matter how much I [ __ ] on
una persona por mucho me me cag yo en
Twitter no matter how much without a father no matter how
Twitter por mucho sin padre por mucho
crazy No matter how much this moves the looks
loca Por mucha movida de esto las pintas
of a person will never tell you what they
de una persona nunca te van a decir cómo
are like Yes yes it may be that a person
son Sí sí que puede ser que una persona
with certain looks are more likely
con ciertas pintas haya más probabilidad
due to the fact that mostly
por el hecho de que mayoritariamente las
people who have a behavior x are
personas que tienen un comportamientos x
cna a certain aesthetic It can
se cña una estética determinada Puede
happen but not always a person because of
ocurrir pero no siempre una persona por
an appearance that they have no no always no
una pariencia que tenga no no siempre no
always it is like that like me the looks that
siempree es así como yo las pintas que
I have are of face that smells the
tengo yo son de cara que le huele la p
smegma and well in my case Yes but not
smegma y bueno en mi caso Sí pero no
everything or rather any person who  have
todo o sea cualquier persona que tenga
good nobody should blame their
bueno nadie debería recriminar a su
partner see their new friends
pareja ver a sus nuevos amigos solo
you can only talk about it now being
puedes hablarlo ahora que siendo unos
new friends I would have cut my
nuevos amigos yo hubiera cortado mi
relationship with them because my partner is
relación con ellos porque mi pareja está
uncomfortable and their intentions are evident Yeah of
incómoda y se ve sus intenciones Sí
course like everyone else your partner
claro como todo el mundo tu pareja te
tells you Hey, I'm insecure that you talk
dice Oye que me qui seguridad que hables
to a guy you know what you want and he says
con un tío sabes que quies fte y te dice
Ah Since I like him go for this
Ah Ya que me cae bien vaya per esto
follow this other thing tell me, I'm insecure that you
seguidad otra cosa que di me qui
go out with your friends that you
seguidad que salgas con tus amigos eso
are a controlling [ __ ] a toxic one of
eres un controlor de [__] un tóxico de
the nu responsibility only of
los nu responsabilidad únicamente de
her but she mixes she she
ella pero ella mezcla ella ella lo
mixes it so that the boy sees it as
mezcla para que el chaval lo vea como
toxicity she the the girl is the
toxicidad ella la la chica esta la
lover of orlock mixes it so that so that
amante de orlock lo mezcla para que para
the boy sees it as toxicity of course
que el chico lo vea como una toxicidad
obviously that's what you're
claro evidentemente es lo que estás
saying Ricky let's see if you take it and one
diciendo Ricky a ver si tú coges y una
thing is that you take it and tell him my
cosa es que tú cojas y le digas me
insecurity what do you think with your friends that that that that
inseguridad que crees con tus amigos que
that friend looks at you like that that
que que que ese amigo te mira así ese
friend looks at you like that you know They are and are the
amigo te mira asá sab Son y son los
friends of the girl of a lifetime Well of
amigos de la chica de toda la vida Pues
course you tell him monkey a kiss that you
claro que se lo digas chango un beso que
tell him from a
se lo digas de un
famous boy who wants to put it in you and
chico famoso que te la quiere meter y
that you know the intention he has and
que tú lo sabes la intención que tiene y
that he is not your friend or anything and that you
que no es tu amigo ni nada y que lo
are getting to know him that you are chatting
estás conociendo que estáis chateando
man eh
hombre eh
man [ __ ] that is not toxicity it is that it is like that it is that
hombre [__] ahí no es toxicidad es que
you have the right to complain I
es así es que tienes derecho a quejarte
say I understand you and I share it I sinned
digo te entiendo y lo comparto yo pequé
of the same absolute trust The thing
de lo mismo confianza absoluta La Movida
is that if after ignoring such
es que si tras ignorar señales tan
clear signs you know that I did not have that my
claras sabes que yo no tuve eso mi
moment you eat the host it is normal to
momento te comes la [__] es normal
imitate it trust the next time like I
imitarla confianza la próxima vez como
consider it completely logical
Considero que es completamente lógico
By the way in relation to this tweet the
Por cierto a colación de este tweet
boy himself responded the
respondió el propio chaval el
protagonist of the story joro says
protagonista de la historia joro dice
you are not wrong because I have said that
razón no te falta porque lo he dicho de
the girlfriend is a [ __ ] and he
que la novia es una [__] y ha un
jumped he says you are not wrong and I have
brincado dice él razón no te falta y se
made it quite clear to him I have
lo he dicho bastante claro te lo he
put it to you with zero intention of offending you
puesto con cero intención de ofenderte
just wanting you to realize how
tan solo con ganas de que te des cuenta
stupid it has been to love and
de la tontería que ha sido querer y
trust someone like that a lot of strength and you
confiar en alguien así mucha fuerza y
will see qu Paz everything that comes now that I have
verás qu Paz todo lo que viene ahora que
lived through that [ __ ] [ __ ] he says I can already
vivido esa [__] [__] dice él ya me
imagine that is why do not worry apart from the fact
imagino por eso no te preocupes aparte
that I am still a boy and I have
que soy aún un chavalito y me queda
a lot to learn both about relationships
mucho por aprender tanto de relaciones
and  Life at least is very
como de la vida por lo menos es muy
positive that the kid was aware
positivo que el chaval fuera consciente
of the situation he was in The
de la situación en la que estaba lo El
kid is younger than her eh I mean she's
chaval es más joven que ella eh O sea
19 But he he
19 Pero él él
looks like he looks 17 or so eh At
parece él parece 17 o así eh Por lo
least in the in the photo that he posted on his
menos en la en la foto que puso en su
Twitter he just lived the way that he
Twitter acaba de vivir de la forma en la
had to process what was coming to him from
que tenía que procesar lo que le venía
now on So I'm happy
ahora en adelante Así que estoy contento
and proud that the kid Well, he
y orgulloso de que el chaval Pues
would have acted like that in that
hubiera de esta manera actuara de esa de
way and in order not to do much more damage
esa forma y por no hacer mucho más daño
to the wound since the girl was
a la herida ya que la chavala se le
leaked because in one of the
filtró todo porque en una de las
conversations you can see her name they
conversaciones se ve su nombre la
found her on Twitter she was the alter ego
encontraron en Twitter era el alterego
of orlock she was like an orlock in girl
de de orlock era como un orlock en chica
on an aesthetic level she was a person who
a nivel de estética era una persona que
hit you so hard on that level So you
pegaba que flipas a ese nivel Entonces
could Ender who wanted to [ __ ] it
se podía Ender que se lo quisiera zumbar
put it in a Story and now they're
poner en un Story and queora me están
slamming me for doing whatever I want
funando por hacer lo que me da la gana
being single Ugh Ugh this would have
estando soltera Uf Uf esto hubiera
made sense if the conversations that
tenido sentido si las conversaciones que
your ex-boyfriend has posted and let's say ex-boyfriend
ha puesto tu exnovio y digamos exnovio
because you were boyfriends didn't look like
porque era hais novios no se viera como
you  you call him boyfriend you tell him but that you
tú lo llamas novio le dices pero que tú
're my boyfriend Eh that you're my boyfriend no no no
eres mi novio Eh que mi novio eres no no
me there boy the girl the girl was
no yo ahí chico la chica la chica estaba
single and the other one has that for Vila it's
soltera y el otro tiene que para Vila es
hard no because you say [ __ ] the other one is to
duro no porque tú dices [__] el otro
blame for having screwed her it's not that it's
tiene culpa de que la hayan puteado no
his fault for having
es que tenga culpa de que la hayan
screwed her but it's that the other one has been
puteado pero es que la otro ha sido más
smarter than
lista que
him it's that it wasn't a serious relationship dude he
él es que no era una relación seria tío
was getting his hopes up he
que le estaba haciendo ilusiones le
was getting his hopes up but son they
estaba haciendo ilusiones pero hijo mío
were telling you right to your
es que te lo estaban diciendo en toda tu
face what it was going to
cara lo que iba a
be you know Let's see if you're walking down the
ser sabes Vamos a ver si tú vas por la
street and this one comes up to you with a really bad
calle y te viene uno con muy malas
appearance Okay and you and and and and with a look
pintas Vale y te y y y y con pinta
[Music]
[Música]
comes and asks you for 1 or 2 or 3 euros no and he
de viene y te pide 1 o 2s o 3 eur no y
asks you for two or 3 euros
te pide dos o 3 euritos
for a monkey Okay and you and he tells you
para para mono Vale y te y te lo dice
clearly He doesn't look at the monkey I don't know what and
claro No mira para el mono no sé cuá y
you say it's that I never have money in
tú dices es que no tengo dinero nunca en
the fed up son and he says Okay then then
lo harto hijo y te dice Bueno pues pues
leave me leave me your cell phone Leave me your iPhone I'm going to I'm going
déjame déjame tu móvil Déjame tu iPhone
there to the corner
que voy a que voy a ir ahí a la esquina
makes a call that  I need
hace una llamada que Necesito que
someone to answer me But I don't want you to
alguien me atienda Pero no quiero que me
hear my call Leave me your phone and
escuches la llamada Déjame tu teléfono y
you pick it up and give it to him Of
tú coges y le das el
course the fault of it being
teléfono claro la la culpa de que te lo
stolen is not yours Of course the one who does it
roben no es tuya claro el el que lo hace
wrong is the one who steals it from you Of course but you
mal es el que te roba Claro pero tú lo
might as well have given it to him a little bit not that he does it to
mismo se la se la has regalado un poco
you No well this is a
no que te lo haga no pues esto es un
little bit like that man I mean in that sense
poco así tío o sea yo en ese sentido
I'm with her it's not a relationship I mean it's
estoy con ella no es una relación o sea
a relationship but it's not a
es una relación pero no es una relación
serious and stable relationship or anything like that it's a
seria y estable ni nada por el estilo es
relationship where she's laughing
una relación de que ella se está riendo
in his face You say hi very very loudly
en la cara de él Tú saludo mu muy fuerte
to joro he has to file for the next
a joro tiene que filar para la próxima
time because I think it's quite a
vez porque creo que tiene bastante
crime to have allowed his partner so much
delito haberle permitido tantísimo a su
when it's so clear But anyway,
pareja cuando la tan clar Pero en fin yo
for my part I also see this situation
por mi parte también veo esta situación
Ah from the outside I don't see it as
Ah desde fuera que yo no lo veo como una
infidelity that you say you know hosa
infidelidad que tú digas sabes hosa me
has failed me I don't know what I suppose I influence it
ha fallado no sé qué Supongo que incido
in a different way although I'm
de una manera diferente aunque estoy
completely sure that if my
completamente seguro de que si mi
story or my character development
historia o mi desarrollo de personaje
as some are calling it Would have
como lo está llamando alguno Hubiera
come out in a different way via
salido de una manera distinta vía
Exactly the same of  this that I just
Exactamente lo mismo de esto que acabo
read because it's pretty heavy and
de leer porque es bastante heav y
pretty obvious But well I also
bastante evidente Pero bueno también
wanted to comment on something And it is that one
quería comentar una movida Y es que uno
of the oslo has not said anything What is he going to
de los oslo no ha dicho nada Qué qué va
say about the hate movements that I have seen
a decir de movimientos que he visto de
is quite personal the issue
odio es bastante en lo personal el tema
of why start talking to a
de que porque empezar a hablar con una
19 20 year old girl maybe the
chavala de 19 20 años puede que la
girl didn't tell him that she had a boyfriend that she did
chavala no le dijese que tenía novio que
n't tell him did zumb barrs
no se lo dijo hiz zumb barrs la mayor
most of the criticism fell on him
parte de la crítica le cayese a él a él
many people saying that they are minors
muchísima gente poniendo que sea menores
many people saying that they were
muchísima gente diciendo que eran
pedophiles many people making jokes
pedófilo muchísima gente haciendo bromas
about daughters and about little girls it's a
sobre hijas y sobre niñas pequeñas es un
bit luckily I know that because of the sense
poco por suerte Yo sé que por el sentido
of humor that losl has he will read these
del humor que tiene losl va leer estas
things and even he himself will laugh at what they
cosas y hasta el mismo se rira de las
write but it's quite unpleasant that
que ponen pero bastante desagradable que
people call you a pedophile for sleeping with
la peña te llame pedófilo por tirarte
a 20 year old girl I think that
una chavala de 20 años creo que la mayor
most of the criticism has been eaten by
parte de la crítica se la hab comido el
Papo for having slept with an
Papo por haber se tirado una chavala
older girl who was hitting on him
mayor de edad que le tiraba la caña a él
and that was even  your city to sleep with your
y que fue hasta su ciudad para tirársela
boyfriend, I find it disgusting, honestly
novio me parece asqueroso la verdad
disgusting. Well, what am I going to say? It's
asqueroso Per bueno qu voy a decir yo
normal that I'm shocked, they
normal que me qued estus mos a mí
're always calling me all kinds of things for
siempre me están llamando de todo por
telling me whoever the [ __ ] I want,
contarme con quién me da la [__] gana
of course, adults and anyway, I
por supuesto mayores de edad y en fin
don't have much more to comment on, I'm Ricky
noy mucho más que comentar yo soy Ricky
and I don't have any Ricky just defended,
y no tengo cer Ricky acaba de defender
I ask, uh, I ask but just like that,
pregunto eh pregunto pero así nada más
by chance, Ricky just just
que por casualidad Ricky acaba de acaba
defended Orlock, no, that it
de defender a orlock no que que le
seems wrong to you that Orlock, at 30,
parece mal que orlock con 30 se haya
slept with a 19 year old,
tirado a una de 19
no, and you think it's terrible, no, you
no y le parece fatal que no que le
think it's terrible that people are
parece fatal que la gente le esté
telling him, criticizing him, not because of the
diciendo le esté criticando no por la
age difference, don't confirm it, he just
diferencia de edad no confirmarme lo
did it, no, like he did with
acaba de hacer no como lo hizo con el
Chostas, too, didn't he just
chocas también
do it? Ricky,
no lo acaba de hacer Ricky
right? No, but I'm just saying it out of
verdad no pero lo digo solo por
curiosity,
curiosidad
uh, him and that he went all the way to his [ __ ] city
eh a él y que fue hasta su [__] ciudad
to sleep with her, he's totally fine, let's see
para tirársela comido el pavo por ha ver
if he slept with an adult girl who was
si tirado una chavala mayor de edad que
hitting on him and that he went all the way to
le tiraba la caña a él y que fue hasta
his [ __ ] city to sleep with his boyfriend, I
su [__] ciudad para tirársela novio me
find it disgusting  the truth is disgusting
parece asqueroso la verdad asqueroso
but well I'm going to say my norms that I'm that estmos they
pero bueno voy a decir yo norms que me
are always
que estus mos a mí siempre me están
calling me everything to get angry with whoever
llamando de todo por enarm con quién me
the [ __ ] hell I want of course
da la [__] gana por supuesto mayores de
adults and there's not much more to comment on I
edad y no hay mucho más que comentar yo
am
soy
Ricky says Mr. J Dallas also said it
Ricky dice señor J también lo dijo
Javi what did Dallas say to him I mean
Dallas Javi el qué le dijo Dallas o sea
Dallas got involved with the age difference
Dalas se metió con la diferencia de edad
or defended that nothing happened because of the
o defendió que no pasaba nada por la
age difference no no I this I agree
edad no no yo esto yo estoy de acuerdo
with what Ricky said it seems to me
en lo que ha dicho Ricky a mí me
that the two of them can be whatever the hell
parece que pueden ha ser los dos lo que
they want obviously
les dé la gana evidentemente
Dallas also said it Javi stop being
Dallas también lo dijo Javi deja de ser
moralistic but Mr. J you are not
moralista pero seor J tú no estás
listening to what we are saying what did
escuchando lo que estamos diciendo qué
Dallas say about
es lo que dijo Dallas de la
age Dallas said the same thing man of
edad Dallas dijo lo mismo hombre
course man Of course but if it's not you can't
claro hombre Claro pero si es que no no
mess with him because
te puedes meter con orlo porque se
because he sleeps with a girl of legal
porque se acueste con una chica mayor de
age Of course
edad Claro que
not Of course not obviously
no Claro que no evidentemente
but the thing is that Ricky has done it on other occasions
pero es que Ricky en otras ocasiones sí
Ricky has done it on other occasions let's say
hecho Ricky en otras ocasiones sí la ha
not to sleep with someone
hecho vamos no por acostarse con alguien
but because for less by
sino porque por menos por
chat I I agree with what
chat yo Yo estoy de acuerdo con lo que
Ricky said not now  with what
ha dicho Ricky ahora no con lo que dijo
Ricky said on other occasions, he
Ricky en otras ocasiones al chocas
also defended Chosas when it came out that
también lo defendió cuando salió que el
Chosas was supposedly hooking up with a
choca se supone que había ligado con una
girl who they said was 19 and he was
chica que decían que tenía 19 y él tenía
30, he also defended him, rcky I don't know
30 también lo defendió el el rcky no sé
what noo and he got offended with the people who
qué noo y se ofendió con la gente que le
said
dijo
things to him, they're not understanding What do you
cosas no están entendiendo A qué te
mean? Well, I'm not going to
refieres Bueno pues yo ya no voy a
talk about that subject anymore but it's to
hablar de ese tema pero es para
keep it to myself it's to keep it to myself it's to keep it to
guardármelo es para guardármelo
myself the double standards eh
es para guardármelo la doble moral eh
So you can see that you
Para que tú veas que no hay que echa
never pay attention to what
cuenta nunca lo que
you Let's see, let's see another
te A ver vamos a ver otra
little thing,
cosilla
Maichi Maichi denies being mistreated
maichi maichi desmiente ser maltratada
due to a hoax from her hater Ah This is what
por bulo de su hater Ah Esto es lo
yes yes Exactly Ricky called me everything
que sí sí Exacto Ricky me llamó de todo
when
a mí cuando
that but a week before he had
eso pero una semana antes había
defended I think he was around there at
defendido al creo que estaba por ahí por
the same time, what about Maichi is that the
el mismo tiempo lo de maichi es que el
other
otro
day Luar was without audio and he is without
día estaba sin audio luar y está sin
audio, he is without audio the same as Maichi
audio está sin audio igual lo de maichi
Luare is without audio the same man, he is without audio, he is
luare está sin audio igual
without audio man what time
tío está sin está sin audio tío qué hora
is it
es las
9 we still have
9 todavía tenemos
[Music]
[Música]
a a  little while
un un ratillo
eh
eh
obviously Elvia but that wasn't what we
evidentemente Elvia pero no era eso de
were talking about we were
lo que se estaba hablando se estaba
talking about
hablando de las
ages if I were talking about what
edades si estuviera hablando de lo que
you're saying I'll shut up I know he has nothing to
tú dices me me callo se no tiene nada
say But what other
que opinar Pero qué otro
topic I mean Nimu is like a real hater of
tema o sea nimu está como muy hater del
dwine
dwine
eh he's a real hater of rewind they
eh está muy hater del del rewind han
released
sacado hoy
the poster today wait let's see the
el el cartel espera vamos a ver el
poster Look I saw it
cartel Que fíjate que lo he visto yo
just before
justo antes
before opening I saw the poster
de antes de abrir he visto el el cartel
Look rigan
Mira rigan
hispano we saw the trailer the other day
hispano el tráiler lo vimos el otro día
Okay right now they're at the premiere
Vale ahora mismo están en la premiere
again stuck
otra vez encallado
okay I
vale
love it it's cool it was
me encanta el es molón era
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
cool okay places King the
almolón vale lugares Rey el
protagonist listen to me look this is the
protagonismo escúchame mira este es el
poster okay look I saw it just
cartel vale mira yo lo he visto justo
before opening the live and the truth
antes de de abrir el directo y la verdad
is I thought the design was at least
me ha parecio el diseño por lo menos
super cool
super chulo
now the logo here of Taki on the whole
ya el logo aquí de Taki en en todo el
poster is so big
cartel tan grande
[Music]
[Música]
eh Now the logo here of Taki is so big eh Let's
eh Ya el logo aquí de Taki tan grande eh
see the poster is very nice as for the
A ver el cartel está muy guapo lo que es
design it's not bad
el diseño no está mal
okay That's the only thing  you
vale Así lo único
see the shoka would be the protagonist not
verá el shoka sería el protagonista no
like Indiana joh Barbie is cristinini
en plan Indiana joh Barbie es cristinini
ok
OK
here plex comes out River comes out with the theme of the
aquí sale plex sale River con el tema de
boeo
la del boeo
no these three I don't know what they
no estos tres no sé qué es lo que
interpret okay El Rubius who said he was
interpretan vale El Rubius que dijo que
n't going to come out comes out disguised as aen
no iba a salir sale disfrazado de aen
and he Joan
y he Joan
pradels
pradels
jados and Kiko Rivera
jados y Kiko Rivera
no I mean let's see is it Kiko Rivera or is it
no O sea vamos a ver es Kiko Rivera o es
someone who looks like Kiko Rivera on
alguien que se parece a Kiko Rivera en
the poster but it's not Kiko Rivera it's Kiko
el cartel pero no es Kiko Rivera es Kiko
Rivera
Rivera
right is Kiko Rivera right Let's
verdad es Kiko Rivera
see of course the poster is nice I have too
verdad A ver claro el cartel está guapo
much of him I have too much of him let's see It's not that I have too much of him
me sobra el me sobra a ver No es que me
because I don't care No but
sobre porque a mí me da igual No pero ya
El Taki there it
El Taki ahí te te
grates on you now the tais there it grates on you a
chirría ya el tais ahí te chirría un
little you know but since they give him so much
poco sabes pero ya que le den tanto
prominence I understand that jados has
protagonismo yo entiendo que jados ha
been a great meme not a great character
sido un gran meme no un gran personaje
So they have taken it as a meme
Así que se lo han tomado como meme
During this year but Kiko Rivera on the
Durante este año pero Kiko Rivera en el
poster Kiko Rivera on the poster dressed
cartel Kiko Rivera en el cartel vestido
In addition to Ken because he is dressed as
Además del Ken porque está vestido del
Ken, plex has
Ken el plex tiene la camiseta de
Francua's shirt okay
francua vale
eh  He's handsome, he's handsome, the truth is He's
eh Está guapo está guapo la verdad Está
handsome, let's see what comes out tomorrow, we'll
guapo vamos a ver qué sale mañana lo
see. The only thing that
veremos lo único
shocked me is Kiko Rivera
así que me ha chocado es Kiko Rivera
because Kiko Rivera has had a leading role, let's see, from
porque Kiko Rivera qué protagonismo ha
respect, eh
tenido a ver desde desde el respeto eh
from respect because in
desde el respeto porque de
fact, for me, for us, for the
hecho para mí para nosotros para la
people who follow telesalseo, the
gente que seguimos telesalseo la
interview Jordi's podcast w la Kiko
entrevista El podcast de Jordi w la Kiko
Rivera, well, it has been the podcast of the
Rivera pues ha sido el podcast del del
year, for the Wild project, I think,
año de los de Wild project yo creo
because for us it was an
porque para nosotros fue un salseo
incredible amount of gossip and a lot of headlines, but
increíble y un montón de titulares pero
as a leading role, for
como protagonismo del del
gossip, as a leading role, for gossip and the
chisme como protagonismo del chisme y
streamer world, not from this
del del mundo streamer no de este grupo
elite group. Kiko Rivera, yes, Kiko Rivera
de la élite Kiko Rivera si Kiko Rivera
has really forced his role by getting closer and
ha forzado mucho el rol por acercarse y
by hanging out with the streamers, they
por juntarse con los streamers lo
led him to the disaster, you know.
llevaron a lo del disaster sabes
But well, you V, there's a cameo with El
Pero bueno tú V hay un cameo con El
Rubius, no also and such,
Rubius no también y tal
well, well, let's
bueno
see, it looks like it's
bueno a ver tiene pinta de que está
cool, okay. Yes, it's true that the
chulo vale Sí que es verdad que la
contradiction is not And the hypocrisy of
contradicción no Y la hipocresía de con
everything they've given. Oh, the brands are not
todo lo que han dado Ay las marcas no
going to contaminate my video, I don't know what's
van a contaminar mi vídeo no sé qué
good. Well, in the end, through the mouth  dies the
bueno Pues al final por la boca muere el
p and and so on Look El
p y y demás Mira El
Rubius okay There you have it for some
Rubius vale Ahí lo tenéis que por algún
reason he said he wasn't going to be there but
motivo dijo que no iba a estar pero ya
the sign already came out that he was going to be there
salió el cartel de que sí iba a estar
eh gref the
eh gref el
biggest winner
ganador mayor
Sia let's see what
Sia a ver qué es
this is it's like it's a fight here they
esto es como si fuera una pelea aquí
're simulating like a fight damn
están simulando como una pelea [__]
because let it be up in the air whoever it is
porque que sea hasta por los aires el
up in the
que sea hasta por los
air
aires
Vegeta quakiti
Vegeta quakiti
auron
auron
cristinini
cristinini
dros sasa the
dros sasa el
Italian Who
italiano Quién
is it I don't know who it is but here there's a
es no sé quién es pero aquí hay un
counter of
contador
course this is that movie open
claro es que esta es la peli esa de open
open I don't know what no it's that I haven't seen it
open no sé qué no es que no la he visto
dude I haven't seen it I haven't seen it and I don't
tío no la he visto no lo he visto y no
understand the reference won't be that no
entiendo la la referencia no será eso no
but well it will be cool for sure it will be
pero bueno estará Guay seguro estará
cool for sure
Guay seguro
man it will be cool The Movida is that nimu well this is
hombre estará Guay La Movida es que nimu
quite a hater nimu okay
pues está está bastante hater nimu vale
What the hell is this I mean nimmo the other
Qué [__] es esto O sea nimmo el otro
day posted some tweets I don't know if you
día puso un unos tweet no sé si me
've sent me more because they were
habréis mandado más porque me estaban
sending me in the group like more tweets no
mandando en el grupo como más twit no
nimu the other day posted a series of
nimu el otro día puso puso una serie de
tweets complaining it's your rewind it doesn't
twit quejándose es vuestro rewind no
represent  to no one the truth
representa a nadie la verdad
and your rewi doesn't represent anyone you guys
e vuestro rewi no representa a nadie
are
sois una
[ __ ] it's not the rewind of the people it's
[__] no es el rewind de del pueblo es
just the rewind of your friends
solamente el rewind de tus amigos
only no something like that no and it's like Yes
solamente no algo así no y es como Sí
really yes or I mean really what am I telling you
realmente sí o sea realmente qué te digo
eh one second I think there was another
eh un segundo que creo que había otro
tweet okay I'm
tweet vale
going to be
voy
clear It's that this look says nimu says
claro Es que esto mira dice nimu le dice
to someone responding to what the
a alguien respondiendo a lo de Qué
hell is this he says to someone if you
[__] es esta le dice a alguien si
want they put you with delox and Dallas
quieres te ponen a ti con delox y Dallas
and says nimu no kidding we were more
y dice nimu fuera broma fuimos más
relevant than half of the
relevantes que la mitad de los del
poster
póster
totally but
totalmente pero
totally It's that this is like this What is
totalmente Es que esto sí es así Qué es
a gref video we already know it's a
un vídeo de gref ya lo sabemos es un
video of Alex cool who is a fan of
vídeo de Alex molón que es un fan de
gref a big fan of gref okay
gref muy fan de gref vale Ya lo
We've been watching it many times and we've
Estuvimos viendo muchas veces y hemos
seen that uh Well he's a fan of gres he
visto que eh Bueno es un fan de gres
even wanted to do that dirty thing that they were going to
incluso quiso hacer la guarrada esa que
be
que iban a ser
and wanted to be that dirty thing that they were going to be to keep
e quizo ser la guarrada esa que iban a
it gre the credit and
ser para para quedárselo gre el mérito y
release it on his Twitch you understand
estrenarlo en su Twitch me entiendes
deceiving all the rest of the
engañando a todo el resto de de
youtubers me I to me what I can't get my
youtubers yo yo a mí lo que no me entra
head around okay is that
en la cabeza vale es que eso no pasará
nothing will happen dude I mean here things
nada tío o sea aquí es que las cosas
depend on who does them okay I mean a guy
depende Quién las haga vale o sea un tío
like
como el
shas a guy like chocas a girl like
shas un tío como el chocas una tía como
cristinini a guy like Jordi wil a guy
cristinini un tío como Jordi wil un tío
like Rubius d Mario and Jo
como Rubius d Mario y Jo
Juan okay pl he won't have a clue about this
Juan vale pl no tendrá ni idea de esa
thing okay But and I Juan did know about it
movida vale Pero y yo Juan sí lo supo
Rubius too Jordi wil too and
Rubius también Jordi wil también y
shokas too kini probably also
shokas también kini seguramente también
okay I mean they do something dirty to you
vale o sea te hacen una guarrada así
okay I mean you're going to
vale o sea tú vas a
collaborate for free because people say
colaborar gratis porque la gente dice
this isn't like this is from the
que esto no es que esto es de la
community no it's not like this is from the
comunidad no es que esto es de la
community it's a video from the community
comunidad es un vídeo de la comunidad
that isn't from the community it's a video from that
que no es de la comunidad es un vídeo
guy who has also promoted his
del chico ese que además ha impulsado su
company okay of
empresa vale de
audiovisual productions has
producciones audiovisuales la ha
promoted it Thanks to all of you who
impulsado Gracias a todos ustedes que lo
have promoted it for
habéis promocionado
free I mean to me eh I think the video is very cool
gratis O sea a mí eh Me parece muy chulo
I think the video is great
el vídeo me parece genial el vídeo
[Music]
[Música]
eh to me probably on some occasions I wouldn't have
eh a mí seguramente en alguna ocasión no
liked I mean I wouldn't have minded
me hubiese gustado O sea no me hubiese
Maybe I would participate if it was
importado A lo mejor participar si fuera
something that didn't cost me work and didn't
algo que no me costase trabajo y no me
cost me anything but that's another thing  the
supona nada pero ya el otra cosa es la
people who fight their asses off to be
gente que se parta la cara por por estar
there like if that were something official okay
ahí como Si eso fuera algo oficial vale
eh And more than the guy trying to deceive you I mean I do
eh Y más que el tío te intente engañar o
n't know if I'm explaining myself it's that of course the
sea no sé si me explico es que claro la
people who maybe don't understand the
gente que a lo mejor no entiende
people who don't understand this
del la gente que no entiende del del
world of work this what we do
mundo este del trabajo este a lo que nos
Well maybe they don't see the
dedicamos Pues a lo mejor no ve la la
filth but let's see I'm the
guarrerías pero vamos a ver yo soy el
shas or El Rubius okay And I say Okay
shas o El Rubius vale Y yo digo Bueno
okay like in this video
venga vale como este vídeo participan
everyone participates or at least everyone
todos o por lo menos todos los del
around us everyone who moves
entorno nuestro todos los que se mueven
in the same circle and everyone participates for
en el mismo círculo y y todos participan
free okay because they have considered it
gratis vale porque lo han considerado
as the community video well
como el vídeo de la comunidad bueno
come on it's a free promo all over
venga va es una promo gratuita por toda
the face not only for the
la cara ya no solamente al Canal del
guy's Channel but so that the guy makes money
chico sino para que gane dinero el chico
but also eh the
sino para que además eh lo reviente la
guy's company can break it Chico has a
empresa del chico Chico tiene una
company that makes HM Well he makes
empresa que hace HM Bueno pues hace
videos and makes ads for example they have
vídeos y hace anuncios por ejemplo la
hired him for many things not that it's
han contratado para muchas cosas no que
very good okay but but you
está muy bien vale pero pero tú
collaborate for free with the excuse that oh
colaboras gratis con la excusa de que ay
the community the community is a video of
la comunidad la comunidad es un vídeo de
the community okay And now on top of that the
la comunidad vale Y ahora encima el
owner of the Channel the one who makes the video and
dueño del Canal el que hace el vídeo y
greev they want to deceive you and without telling you
greev te quieren engañar y sin deciros
anything without telling you anything gref is
nada sin deciros nada gref lo está
paying for it with the condition that he broadcasts it
pagando con la condición de que lo emite
on his channel and will do a Willy Red
en su canal y hará ahí un Willy Red
collaborating a Jordi W with collaborating
colaborando un Jordi W con colaborando
a Rubius collaborating without knowing that they are
un Rubius colaborando sin saber que
giving away a collaboration to
están regalándole una colaboración a
gref it's incredible it's not incredible no Ah
gref es increíble no es increíble no Ah
But well that's it because nothing happens
Pero bueno ya está por pues no pasa nada
we look the other way like the one who did it
miramos para otro lado como el que lo ha
gref well between us we
hecho gref pues entre nosotros no nos
can never see each other But well man and it's the same old thing
podemos ver nunca Pero bueno tío y es lo
once again eh it's the same old thing
de siempre una vez más eh es lo de
once again I have things that I don't
siempre una vez más yo son cosas que no
understand eh I don't know if it's that I'm
entiendo eh yo no sé si es que yo soy
really bad vibes very argumentative or whatever you
muy mal rollero muy peleón o lo que sea
know trust you but I Afterwards I am the
sabes fíate tú pero yo Después soy la
least resentful person in the world but
persona menos rencorosa del mundo pero
one thing is that and another thing is that I
una cosa es esa y otra cosa ya es que me
took it for a fool I mean you know that there have
tomé de tonto o sea ustedes sabéis que
been cases in which they have
ha habido casos en los que me han
tried to do the 131 on me and and I feel
intentado hacer la 131 y y me sienta
terrible I mean one thing is it's for the good of how
fatal o sea una cosa es por las buenas
good I am I'm a fool of how
de bueno de bueno que soy soy tonto de
good I am I'm a fool okay
bueno que soy soy tonto vale
And you ask for my hand and I let you
Y me pides la mano y te dejo que me
hold me  up to my shoulder but since you
cojas hasta el hombro pero ya que me lo
did it by deceiving me there I feel bad
hagas engañándome ahí ya me sienta mal
you know and what
sabes y lo
about CCU do you think CCU will appear in the video
de ccu creéis que saldrá ccu en el vídeo
yes it will no and what about IB
sí saldrá no y lo de lo de IB
presenting the chimes with Gref they
presentando las campanadas con gref se
were fighting less than two months ago
estaban peleando hace menos de dos meses
with things that were very
con cosas que eran muy
ugly I mean they are
feas o sea son cosas
things that a person with whom
que son cosas que una persona con la que
you have good vibes you don't get involved with this
tú tienes buen rollo no te tiras el tema
this tax issue I put it in the
este de los impuestos lo he puesto en el
news then you see it I mean and it goes all over your
noti luego lo veis o sea y va por toda
face he threw it at Gref Yes yes well you do
la cara le tiró a gref Sí sí pues haces
like Gref who spends more days in
como el gref que te pasa más días en
Spain than in Andorra but you pay taxes in
España que en andorra pero tributas en
Andorra and Gres responds or like
andorra y el gres le responde o como
Olai who pays taxes like a company I don't know
olai que tributa como una empresa no sé
what I mean with people with whom I have good
qué O sea yo con la gente que tengo buen
vibes I mean me I wouldn't play those jokes with Dallas
rollo o sea yo yo con Dallas no me
you can play
gastaría esas bromas te puedes gastar
ugly jokes I don't know what I don't know how much you know
bromas feo no sé qué no sé cuánto sabes
but those jokes in public no you don't
pero esas bromas en público no no te las
mess around with a person who has more or
gachas con una persona que tiene más o
less good vibes let's say not even with a person with whom you
menos buen rollo vamos ni ni con una
don't have good vibes nor with
persona que no tengas buen rollo ni con
a person who doesn't have bad vibes you spend
una persona que no tengas malo te gastas
those jokes and now they're both there in
esas bromas y ahora están los dos ahí en
less than two months you know the
menos de dos meses vete tú a saber el
contract company that's in between you know
contrato empresa que hay por media sabes
and And now you're there
y Y ahora estás ahí
eh presenting on your channel the
eh presentando en tu canal la la
bell man I have to go to the bathroom go
campanada tío tengo que ir al baño vá
to the monster
tel el monster
eh
eh
starting tomorrow there's no m or
a partir de mañana es que ya no hay m ni
motor or m or
motor ni m ni
already tomorrow when I have the schedule
ya mañana cuando tenga el horario
recovered today I have done the diet
recuperado ya hoy he hecho la dieta otra
again perfect yesterday too and already the at the
vez perfecta ayer también y ya el en el
moment
momento
that at the moment
que en el momento
of I'll tell you tomorrow soda out the
de te lo diré mañana refresco fuera el
problem is that it's it's in the middle
problema es que está la está por medio
of Christmas Eve no Well of course the
de la Nochebuena no Bueno claro el
problem is that it's in the middle of
problema es que está por medio de la
Christmas Eve it's going to be ruined for me one day here and there it's
Nochebuena se me va estropear un día por
going to be ruined for me a little bit there and there's
medio se me va a estropear un dita por
no let's see there was one
ahí por medio no a ver había una cosilla
more thing that we had to
más que nos quedaba por
see where are you je what have I done
ver dónde estás jé qué he hecho
Javier
Javier
lo Ah look there was also a roll
lo Ah mira que había un rollo también
with Jord there
con jord
was a roll with Jordi
había un rollo con Jordi
Wild for having removed his his category or
Wild por haber quitado su su categoría o
rather the elan the
sea los elan los
elan already was it already was but but they
elan ya lo era ya lo era pero pero
let Jordi pass but the elan were
dejaron pasar a Jordi pero los elan eran
only for live content
solo para contenido en
the elan were only for
los elan eran solo para contenido en
live content what happened was that
directo lo que lo que pasó fue que a
Jordi was slipped in like in
Jordi pues se lo colaron como en
[Music]
[Música]
plan I don't know why because he had done one
plan no sé por qué porque había hecho un
live show a year I don't remember what Because
directo al año no me acuerdo qué Porque
Jordi's thing is never live They are
lo de Jordi Nunca es directo Son son
premieres they are fake live shows and
extrenos son falsos directos y y a ver
let's see what you think about the fact that there is no more
vamos a ver qué opin de que de que ya no
Talk show Of course they have removed the
Talk show Claro que han quitado la
category directly no also not
categoría directamente no también ya no
only the possibility of
solamente la posibilidad de de El
winning it without doing a live show but the
ganarlo sin hacer directo sino la
category Well let's go with the
categoría Bueno vamos con los
esan what's wrong
esan qué te pasa
with me with my face all smiles and
conmigo con la cara todo sonrisas y
smiles and jokes such a Jord crack total and
sonrisas y bromas tal jord crack total y
then
luego
eliminating my category well let's see what
eliminando mi categoría bueno a ver qué
happened here there has been a
ha pasado aquí ha habido una
restructuring of the eslan that I don't I don't
reestructuración de los eslan que yo no
know either if they will be the last ones or not do
Tampoco sé si van a ser los últimos o no
you think that it is I think that no I think that
tú crees quees Yo creo que no yo creo
this year it also depends a little
que ya este año depende un poco también
on the toxicity that there is if it goes back to being
de la toxicidad que haya si vuelve a ser
like last year it's better to get tired there's no
como el año pasado mejor se cansa no hay
more but what I do you think that they are
más pero que yo ustedes creen que los
going to be the last ones now or do you think
van a ha serer los últimos ya o creéis
that there will be
que va a haber
more I think it will be forever let's
más yo creo que va a ser para siempre a
see forever you will see It's
ver para siempre verás tú
true that I'm going to say one
Es verdad que igual que voy a decir una
bad thing and another very good thing and it is that it
cosa mala y otra muy buena y es que me
seems much more professional how it is being
parece mucho más profesional como se
done, I think the system Well we will
está haciendo creo que el sistema Bueno
see when it comes but it is not
ya se verá cuando cuando venga pero no
bad there are like two types of
está mal hay como dos tipos de
categories right Some
categorías verdad Unas categorías del
public categories that are going to be funnier the
público que van a ser más chistosas el
anger of the year clip of the year etcetera and
enfado del año clip del año etcétera y
other professional categories not with the
otras categorías profesionales no con el
streamer of the year as the grand prize and the ones
streamer del año como premio gordo y las
that were more prototypical But clar
que eran más prototípicas Pero clar ha
the W project has disappeared which was a
desaparecido la de W project que era
Talk show that sincerely I will talk
Talk show que sinceramente Ya hablaré
to him and ask because I am
con él y preguntaré porque me da
curious to know why he explained it eh it's
curiosidad saber por qué lo explicó eh
that I have not seen it live I have not
es que yo no he visto directo no he
seen bic live I have only seen the
visto directo de bic Yo solo he visto el
post and I have not given myself time n if you look at
post y no me dado tiemp n si tú miras
the Yes why they removed that
los Sí por qué la ha quitado esa
category was valid they are all streamers
categoría era válida todos son streamers
or in other words 100% streaming so the
o sea 100% streaming entonces el
problem is that the majority of podcasts
problema es que la mayoría de podcast no
are not live and it would be very difficult to make
son en directo y sería muy difícil hacer
a category only for live podcasts
una categoría solo de podcast en directo
because there are very few for a
porque son muy poquitos por un
[Music]
[Música]
issue I am that they are
tema Yo es que los
talking to me It's that I do not understand the the the that they
hlan Es que no entiendo el el el que lo
make it only for content  in
hagan solo de contenido en
Stream Why why don't you give awards to
Stream Por qué por qué no das premio a
content creators in general, I
los creadores de contenido en general o
mean, but
sea pero
maybe it's an
igual igual sea un
instagrammer and Aha last year you
instagrammer y Aha el año pasado se lo
give it to the [ __ ] trucks, that dance of
das al foll camiones ese un baile de
streams is a topic that is a bit off
streams es un tema de que se va un poco
topic, okay, well I'm not going to
de la temática vale bueno tampoco voy a
talk about it here either, but I understood that
hablar aquí por pero yo entendí eso
now they make me another clip and they tell me look
ahora me hacen otro clip y me dicen mira
what there is to see on the internet, okay, eh,
lo que hay que ver en internet vale eh
if I'm honest, no, if I'm honest, I'm worth
si te sincero no si sincero me la pena
three quarters of it, there is no category. Hey, it's their
tres cuartos no hay categoría Oye es su
award, do it however you want, I would do it
premios hace como quiera yo lo haría
totally differently from the first
totamente diferente desde el primer
moment, I don't ignore how it is ignored and it
momento yo no obviar como se obvia y
continues to ignore YouTube and the
sigue obvié YouTube y se obvia de una
videos are brutally ignored, but it is
forma brutal los los vídeos pero es es
their award, therefore, of course I do
su premio por lo tanto claro es que yo
not understand why. I mean, since they
no entiendo el Por qué O sea ya que lo
do it, don't include the
hacen no ponlo
entire thing, why wouldn't the elite win? Well, they
entero por qué no ganaría la élite bueno
are their awards, they can do it however they
son sus premios puede hacerlo como le de
want and I imagine they have some
la gana y me imagino que tendrá algún
reason, okay, at least they shouldn't be as
motivo vale por lo menos que no sea tan
shameless as last year when it was, no, not
descara como el año pasado que era no no
just content on Stream but from whoever was
solo contenido en Stream pero de quien
interested in including it and that Stream
le interesaba meterlo y que no si Stream
included it Then  he does it how he wants he
lo metía Entonces lo hace como quiere
wants to do Stream only fantastic
quiere hacer Stream solo fantástico
perfect when he's interested in returning to
perfecto cuando le interese volver a
YouTube and making videos again There he's going to
YouTube y vuelve a hacer vídeos Ahí va a
do it again no and it's normal [ __ ] if
hacer otra vez no y es normal [__] si
in the end he finances it it's not that it's
al final lo financia él no es que es un
his video Of course it's not something official
vídeo suyo Claro que no es algo oficial
or it's not going to be someone else who imposes it
o no va a ser otro el que le imponga
but I eat or I mean at the level of opinion it
pero yo como o sea yo a nivel de opinión
seems to me it seems like a bad way to
me parece un me parece un mal camino
ignore such interesting categories and that
obviar categorías tan interesantes y que
can even give so much cach some
incluso pueden dar tanto cach unos
awards like things like
premios como pueden ser cosas como
documentary videos would have been
vídeos documentales hubiera estado
Great podcast that where there is [ __ ] the
Genial podcast que donde hay [__] el
podcast not in this one in many podcasts you
podcast no en este en muchos podcasts
can find super
puedes encontrarte información super
interesting information reason why
interesante razón por la que
Dear already but don't you think that because the
Dear ya pero no crees que porque por
way you tell it the event would be greatly enriched by
como lo contáis se enriquecería mucho el
including an event while choosing
evento de incluir evento mientras elegir
Don how far do you go you know I mean you have to
Don hasta dónde llegas sabes O sea
put a limit somewhere
tienes que poner un límite en algú sitio
but t show I understand the category is
pero t show Yo entiendo la categoría es
complicated and I understand a category of
complicada y entiendo una categoría de
live shows of a variety of
shows en directo de variedad de
news are direct direct you know it
informativos son directos directos sabes
's not Ed can't ha it's that
no es Ed no puede
such a show of course it was a
ha es que tal show claro es que era una
was a good category but of
era una buena categoría pero
course it is that he
claro es que
should well he should let's see he can do
debería bueno debería a ver puede hacer
whatever he wants not it  that we are talking about
lo que quiera no lo que estamos hablando
but that would be good
pero que estaría bien
[Music]
[Música]
HM what is
HM de qué está hablando
Lorena talking about Lorena says she is a criminal
Lorena Lorena dice es una criminal
good but bad face who are you
carita buena pero mala de quién estás
talking about and this is a live What's going on
hablando y esto es un directo Qué pasa
who are you talking about this is a
de quién estáis hablando esto es un
live eh the category such show is
directo eh la categoría tal show se
removed basically for three
quita básicamente por tres motivos
main reasons the first had a winner and
principales el primero tenía ganador y
they don't like it, I mean the W project was the
no les gusta o sea el W project era el
winner, we know it here those of us who
ganador est lo sabemos aquí los que
are here as is I don't think you have
estamos aquí tal cual yo no creo que ha
found a ball cat of The
encontraste una gata de pelotas de El
Wild project was the winner But why
Wild project era ganador Pero por qué
was Wild project the winner because of the
era ganador Wild project por el tema
visits no because it is the one with the most visits let's
visitas no porque es el que más visitas
see the nude of project nude no I don't
tiene a ver el nud de project nude no no
know if it will be pronounced like that that one also
sé si se pronunciará así ese también
has a podcast with a lot of visits And
tiene podcast con muchísimas visitas Y
that one is also very good and it has
ese también está muy bien y ha
achieved me, for example, I like the
conseguido a mí por ejemplo me gustan
characters that
más los personajes que ha conseguido
nude project has achieved more, nude project is called No, for
nude project nude project se llama No a
example, for my thing, I like the
mí por ejemplo para mi rollo me gusta
ones that nude has achieved more
más los que ha conseguido
than Jordi Jordi is a little more
que que Jordi Jordi es un toquecito más
serious
serio
No The fact was terrifying and the
No Fue terrorífico el hecho de y el
nude this has brought more influencers
nude este ha traído más más influencers
and actors
y actores
Look Crazy this was
Mira Loco este fue
brutal this was
brutal este fue
brutal What is the
brutal Cuál es el
complete What is  the full one at what
completo Cuál es el completo en qué
time let's see no no the full one is that one
momento a ver no no el completo es
no this one is not the full one no yes yes it is
ese no este no es el completo no sí sí
the full one Look let's see
es el completo Mira a ver
wait well anyway for the
espérate bueno de todas maneras para os
colors no obviously but of course for
colores no evidentemente pero claro para
what for what is our thing for what is
lo que para lo que es nuestro rollo para
our thing Look
lo que es nuestro rollo Mira
[Music]
[Música]
eh
eh
quiqueo
quiqueo
blond mini
blond mini
buller
buller
Paco Len I would love to Paco
Paco León Me encantaría Paco
Len
León
orlock Marta
orlock Marta
Daz Juan
Díaz Juan
Magn Johan parel It's not that I'm
Magán Johan parel No es que me interese
very interested but it's also from the world of
mucho pero es del mundo también de los
youtube Look virus
youtub Mira virus
eye Look
ojo Mira
Ren
René
plex Willy
plex Willy
Rex
Rex
kaidi Nacho
kaidi Nacho
Vidal
Vidal
Fran
Fran
Aitana eye
Aitana ojo
eh but so young No no when I came out I
eh pero así de joven No no cuando salí
was like that for a while how I am very
Estaba así un rato cómo estoy muy
grateful it was damn man Aitana eh come in seen
agradecida fue [__] tío Aitana eh entr
eh I haven't seen that one I haven't
vistón eh ese no lo he visto ese no lo
seen that one eye
visto ojo
eh Nicki Nicole kid How do
eh Nicki Nicole chaval Cómo consiguen
the hippies get these interviews I curse
los hipis estas entrevistas me cago en
my life I mean starting from scratch How do they
mi vida o sea empezando de cero Cómo
get these
consiguen estas
interviews The Casas Brothers
entrevista Los Hermanos
Mara pombo How good eh Well here's
María pombo Qué buena eh Pues aquí hay
a few Antonio
una cuanta Antonio
recio here are a few that I would
recio aquí hay unas cuantas que a mí me
love
encantarían
eh
eh
man and granddaughter you know that I don't
hombre y nieta sabes que a mí no me
like football but how how do
gusta el fútbol pero cómo cómo consiguen
these people get that out of
esta gente esa sacada de de
dick mother of
[__] madre de
God mother of life of course for me it's
Dios madre de la vida claro para mí es
more for me because I don't see anyone
más para mí yo porque no veo a nadie
because I don't have time but for me there
porque no tengo tiempo pero para mí haí
for example I like it
por ejemplo me gusta
more second another problem that the
más segundoo otro problema que los
podcasts vi
podcast vi
won er a lot of
ganado er mucha
difference The difference is 17000
diferencia La diferencia son 17000
podcasts that come after thematic
podcast que vienen después de temática
Jai men are very stupid they don't know How
Jai los hombres son muy tontos no saben
to find the G spot host 17000 the wedge
Encontrar el punto G [__] 17000 la cuñ
important state Oh and the third reason
estado importante Ah y el tercer motivo
is there's everything they want to cover up salvam they
es hay de todo quieren tapar a salvam
want to cover up because But you're not a
quieren tapar porque Pero tú no eres
streamer now well we're still going to But
streamer ahora pues yaun vamos a Pero
how one thing when when it
cómo una cosa cuando cuando incluso
would even be like a defense of my work
sería como una defensa a mi trabajo Por
Why the [ __ ] do you get involved as
qué [__] os metéis vosotros como
victims or I mean the importance of
damnificados o sea la importancia de
talking to you just this year just this
habl vosotros justo este año justo este
year where we're already starting to stand out salv
año donde ya empezamos a despuntar salv
yoto too which today is removed is removed this
yoto too cual hoy se quita se quita este
award is no longer of
premio ya no
interest they were offended they were offended
interesa se ofendieron se ofendieron
because you're not elite anymore but let's see
porque no sos de la élite ya pero a ver
Where do the guys from the podcast come from eh
De dónde salen eh los chicos del podcast
because already  you start the podcast with
o sea porque ya empiezas el podcast con
really strong guests, I
invitados fuertísimos
mean I understand that they're not born from scratch I don't
o sea entiendo que no nacen de cero no
understand that they would already be influencers on
entiendo que ya serían influencer en
other networks or something like that not to
otras redes o algo por el estilo no para
have those contacts mother it's that there in this
tener esos contactos madre es que ahí en
nud there are
en el nud
a few there that I would
este hay unas cuantas ahí que que a mí
love to bring the channel here eh There are
me encantaría traer aquí el canal eh Hay
a few not one or two eh a
unas cuantas no una ni dos eh unas
few that I would love to have
cuantas que a mí me encantaría tener
here one day eh this talk eh some
aquí algún día eh esta charla eh alguno
that I don't like some that I don't like
Que no me alguno Que no me cae bien
also you know
también sabes
some that I hate too okay but
alguno que me ca fatal también vale pero
generally in general eye
general por lo general ojo
Eh well let's see if we can see
Eh bueno vamos a ver si se puede ver lo
Agustn's thing because Agustn's thing has been
de Agustín porque lo de Agustín ha sido
a big move eh I mean he has gone
una movida gorda eh o sea se ha hecho
viral on Twitter with this
viral en Twitter con este
clip all the money he has generated in
clip todo el dinero que haya generado en
the last 15 streams on doxing art and
los últimos 15 streamings en doxe arte e
going to your [ __ ] house Bro I'm going to spend
ir a tu [__] casa Bro me voy a gastar
all the money I have earned in the
todo el dinero que haya ganado en los
last 15 streams okay I mean he's going to
últimos 15 streaming vale o sea va a
calculate half the month and he's going to
calcular la mitad del mes y y se lo va a
spend it on doxing a Random what the hell
gastar en doxear a un Random qué coo
are you saying my family you piece of
estás diciendo mi familia pedazo de
pring out no  I'm serious no no
pring out no te lo digo en serio no no
Explain to me let's get into the
Explícame vamos a entrar en el tema de
family thing what did you say about my family
la familia qué has dicho de mi familia
bro this this is the only context
bro este este es el único contexto que
I was missing what is it here what are you
me faltaba que es lo que aquí a que se
referring to with the family thing you know let's
están refiriendo con tema familia sabes
see Explain to me so that tomorrow I
a ver Explícame para que yo mañana
invest all my money in literally
invierta todo mi dinero en literalmente
doxing a fortnite battle royale name I do
doxar un nombre de fornite Battle royale
n't care if you haven't said anything you have
que no me importa si no has dicho nada
n't said anything about my family now I
no has dicho algo de mi familia ahora
have my balls in place and come back and
tengo los [__] bien puestos y vuel a
repeat it know that I haven't talked about your
repetir sate que yo no he hablado de tu
family because I don't know you I
familia porque yo a ti no te conozco
hope you go away I've been putting up with you for 3 hours you [ __ ] [ __ ] let's
ojalá te vayas llevo 3 horas
see what you
aguantándote [__] subnormal a ver qué te
think I'm your [ __ ] friend What guy
crees que soy tu [__] amigo Qué tío no
aren't you talking about my [ __ ] family bro
estás hablando de mi [__] familia bro
what the [ __ ] is wrong with you dude I don't know who you
qué [__] te pasa tío que no sé quién
are okay And you know who I am let's see
eres vale Y tú sabes quién soy yo a ver
what the [ __ ] is wrong with you dude nothing let's see if I
qué [__] te pasa tío nada a ver si te
see you around here again that I dox you [ __ ] [ __ ]
vuelvo a ver por aquí que te doxeo [__]
the next thing I'm going to do
subnormal lo siguiente que voy a hacer
with you is going to be doxing and put your [ __ ]
contigo va a ser doxear y poner tu [__]
picture on the [ __ ] screen in front of
foto en la [__] pantalla delante de
thousands of people go  to your house
miles de personas ir a tu casa
okay I'm going to spend all the money there is
vale Yo voy a gastar todo el dinero que
buah you
haya buah
know I understand that it's one of these Stream sniping
sabes entiendo que es un Stream sniping
no
de estos no
eh I'm going to see if he explained more
eh voy a ver si hoy ha explicado más
context today come on let's
contexo venga vamos a
listen to him let's see decisive bro [ __ ]
escucharlo a ver decisivo bro de [__]
of and I man but he's going to [ __ ] like a [ __ ]
de y yo tío pero se le va tela de [__]
that I [ __ ] on everything it's true and that
que me cago en todo es verdad y que le
I threaten him is true 40 seconds to
amenazo es verdad 40 segundos para
vent or tomorrow morning I'm going to go
desfogar o mañana por la mañana voy a ir
to the [ __ ] police station and I'm going to show
a la [__] comisaría y voy a enseñar
what happened and I'm going to explain it
hecho que ha pasado y lo voy a explicar
and I'm going to ask him What do I have to do
y voy a preguntarle Qué tengo que hacer
in my place everyone who
en mi lugar todo el mundo que hace
apologizes for it I'm the whole world on
apología la coso todo el mundo de
Twitter
Twitter me
sucks me off and wishes for death
chupár y desea la muerte me
sucks me off control yourself this guy eh look
chupár controlarse este chico eh mira
I'm the same and I've been very bad
que yo soy también y he sido muy mal
soon but I think that Agustn is over me I
pronto pero creo que me supera el
think he's over me eh Because there
Agustín creo que me supera eh Porque ya
are times when I don't see him part of the show or
hay veces que no lo veo parte del show o
rather the show that worked for him and such not
sea el show que le funcionaba y tal no
because of Fortnite and such and people want to
por el fortnite y tal y la gente quiere
see him explode And such But there are times when
verlo explotar Y tal Pero ya hay veces
people [ __ ] me up
que la gente me
Yeah yeah yes I think the same says
por culo Sí sí si yo pienso igual dice
Laura  It's normal for him to get angry but he
Laura Es normal que se enoje pero lo
expresses it very explosively Yeah yeah yeah maybe he
expresa muy explosivo Sí sí si a lo
has more than
mejor tiene motivos más que de
enough reasons you also have to learn a
sobra también tienes que aprender un
little bit already there bullfighting not to the brats
poquito ya ahí toreando no a los niñatos
that sneak into your games
que se te cuelen en la en las partidas
No if it's that you're never going to be able to
No si es que eso no lo vas a poder
stop that not from my [ __ ]
frenar nunca no de mi [__] de mi [__]
favorite game dude to be toxic to another
juego favorito tío a ser tóxico a otro
[ __ ] straight you piece of [ __ ] crazy dude
[__] directo pedazo de [__] zumbado tío
suck my dick dude suck my dick T
chúpame el rabo tío chúpame el rabo T
dude you deserve the worst bro guys all
tío te mereces lo peor bro chicos todo
[ __ ] day dude kids just
el [__] día tío chavales me acaba de
hit me and they give me another decisive snap in the
pegar un y me dan otro snipazo en el
air bro my god
aire decisivo bro madre mía patada
completely decisive kick I mean I don't
completamente decidida O sea no me
regret anything about this
arrepiento de nada de esta
kick I mean I don't regret
patada O sea no me arrepiento de
absolutely anything I mean I would hit it again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and again and I would
absolutamente nada O sea la pegaría otra
hit it again and again and again and again and again I would
la pegaría otra vez y otra vez y otra
hit it 500 times this
vez y otra vez la pegaría 500 veces esta
kick that I just finished  to hit me, I'm bum a
patada que acabo de pegar se me bu un
turkey that I'm going to look for it because I
pavo que lo voy a buscar que me
find a Pro that the Pro leaves me 40
encuentro un Pro que el Pro me deja 40
life from a predi shotgun through
de vida de un escopetazo predit a través
three walls because I'm playing
de tres paredes porque estoy jugando
lobbying of a the annoyance I understand but
lobis de un el mosqueo lo entiendo pero
you start saying that you're going to commit a
te pones a decir que vas a cometer un
crime in the middle of a live because of what happens
delito en pleno directo por lo que pasa
in a game if where there is none is that
en un juego si donde no hay es que
apart from that we're going to see or I mean it's like
aparte que vamos a ver o sea es como
when I had to learn the
cuando yo he tenido que aprender el el
issue of being criticized, being put
tema de que me critiquen que me pongan
down and being defamed which is a shame It's
verde y que me difamen que es una pena
sad the truth It's sad but
Es triste la verdad Es triste pero
you have to take things from whoever
tienes que tomarte las cosas de quien
comes So if you can and you have at hand to
viene Entonces si puedes y tienes a mano
take measures when someone already trespasses
tomar medidas cuando ya alguien traspasa
and you can, then you take measures
y se puede pues tomas las medidas
directly without getting irritated, without getting angry,
directamente sin irritarte sin cabrear
you take measures
tomas medidas
eh And if not, then you have to understand that
eh Y si no pues tienes que entender que
when you are here, there are going to be
que cuando tú estás aquí pues va a haber
anonymous people and random people that you
gente anónima y gente Random que tú no
cannot control eh Nor can you control what they
puedes controlar eh Ni puedes controlar
say to you or what you don't like, or that there
el el que te digan o el que no gustes no
are people who take a dislike to you eh You
el que haya gente que te coja tirria eh
cannot control every comment from
Ni puedes controlar cada comentario de
thousands and thousands of people nor can you
miles y miles de personas ni puedes
pretend  that there isn't a single bad one you
pretender que no haya ni uno malo me
understand me eh There are people who don't ASSUME that
entiendes eh Hay gente que no ASUME eso
For example no and they take it badly Well
Por ejemplo no y lo lleva mal Pues yo
here I see that with Stream sniping
aquí veo que él con el Stream sniping
this he should understand it the same Hey I
este debería entenderlo igual Oye no lo
can't control it some will always
puedo controlar alguno siempre se me va
slip up I laugh at what's done and out you
a colar me río lo hecho y fuera me
understand or I play a couple of jokes
entiendes o le gasto un par de de bromas
to ridicule him and out something like that you know
para ridiculizar y fuera algo así sabes
but it's that he takes it that he doesn't see All
pero es que se lo toma que no vea Todos
the [ __ ] days that he's bitter about the
los [__] días que está amargado con el
Stream sniping issue eh I mean it
tema del Stream sniping eh o sea te
can piss you off obviously it pisses you off but as
puede cabrear evidentemente cabrea pero
many other factors of the
como cabrean muchos otros factores del
game and defs piss you off but anyway
juego y defs pero de todas maneras el
Stream sniping is not
Stream sniping no se
easily solved by putting a delay on the
soluciona fácil poniendo delay al
live I run away because I find one who runs away
directo huyo que me encuentro a uno que
and who snips me the guy that
huyo y que me da un snipazo el tío que
I came looking for and who
yo venía a buscar y que se me ha
bugged me before 5 minutes I'm going to
bugueado antes 5 minutos voy a volver a
kick the table again question
darle una patada a la mesa pregunta
because yesterday a
debido a que ayer se me viralizó un
tweet went viral on basically Twitter that
tweet en básicamente en Twitter que no
has no context and there are
tiene ningún tipo de contexto y hay
a lot of people wishing me dead and such
mucha gente deseándome la muerte y tal
because the clip  it's 40 seconds where I
porque el clip son 40 segundos donde yo
threaten a kid in the
amenazo a un Chaval en la lobby de
fortnite battle royale lobby a kid who
fortnite battle royale un chaval que me
had been harassing me for 8 hours and the
había acosado durante 8 horas y el
context is completely Let's say the
contexto es completamente Vamos o sea el
context is the guy was harassing me and
contexto es el tío estaba acosándome y
then I put him in the lobby and there comes
entonces yo lo meto en la lobby y llega
a time when he messes with my
un momento en el que se mete con mi
family and that's when I get mad and I say dude you
familia y ahí me cabreo y le digo tío te
just went too far okay and I tell him that I'm
acabas de pasar vale y le digo que lo
going to dox him that I don't know what I don't know
voy a doxear que no sé qué que no sé
how much it's worth Okay Hey I haven't done anything I'm
cuánto vale Okay Eh yo no he hecho nada
just telling him so he
simplemente se lo digo para que se
calms down obviously and leaves me
tranquilice obviamente y que me deje en
alone okay I mean I haven't done anything
paz okay O sea yo no he hecho nada
illegal at most I may have threatened him
ilegal como mucho Le habré amenazado
but the thing is that I threatened a guy who has been
pero es que he amenazado un tío que
harassing me for 8 hours So on a
lleva 8 horas acosándome Por lo cual a
legal level if you tell a person
nivel legal si tú le dices a una persona
Yes man I ended up threatening him it's normal he had been harassing me for
Sí tío acabé amenazándolo es normal
8 hours a kiss Mauro and
llevaba 8 horas acosando un beso Mauro y
he messed with my family nothing happens
se metió con mi familia no pasa nada
a tweet appeared Well we've already seen
aparecido un twit Bueno ya hemos visto
that we've
que
already seen that
eso ya hemos visto que eso
if that too You have to control it a
si también lo Tienes que controlar un
little Isabel a
poquito Isabel un
kiss
beso
can soften  the matter can not be an
puede suavizar el asunto no puede ser un
extenuating circumstance let's say no but
atenuante digamos no pero
neither is there that you because a guy you
tampoco tampoco hay que tú porque un tío
know Gets in the game You already
sabes Se te meta en la partida Tú ya
have there Freedom to say I dox you I
tienes ahí Libertad para decir te doxeo
dox you son of a [ __ ] I'm going to put your
te doxeo hijo de [__] voy a poner tu
[ __ ] picture here Twitter a couple of cheat
[__] foto aquí Twitter un par de cheat
po from a couple of pages that I already have
po por parte de un par de páginas que ya
blocked thank God because they
tengo bloqueadas gracias a Dios porque
only bring toxicity and it doesn't happen Although in
solo traen toxicidad y no pasa Aunque en
reality From saying to doing
realidad Del dicho al hecho
absolutely nothing, I mean, one thing is that
absolutamente nada o sea una cosa es que
in the heat of the moment you say that and another is that you
en el calentón digas eso y otra que lo
fulfill it before starting to record is that
cumplas antes de empezar a grabar es que
a guy has created an account from scratch,
un tío se ha creado una cuenta de cero
okay, a completely new account and has
vale una cuenta completamente nueva y se
started doxing, arm yourself, okay, dox yourself, arm yourself, he
ha puesto a doxe arme vale a doxe arme
has put my phone number
ha puesto el mi número de teléfono El
My parents' phone number,
número de teléfono de mis padres el
my brother's phone number and
número de teléfono de mi hermano para
after seeing a tweet without context, he does not
después de ver un tweet sin contexto no
inform himself, he does not see that the other person
informarse no ver que la otra persona le
was accusing him for 8 hours and
estaba acusando durante 8 horas y lo
all you do is [ __ ] try to
único que haces es [__] intentar
screw up that kid's life by
joderle la vida a ese chaval pues
publishing where he lives that I do not live there
publicando dónde vive que no vivo ahí
thank God but oh well it bothers me
gracias a Dios pero bueno me molesta
Likewise his phone number which
Igualmente su número de teléfono que
thank God is not that one  I changed But
gracias a Dios no es ese lo cambié Pero
hey I have another one it doesn't matter I don't want him to
bueno tengo otro da igual No quiero que
take my phone number The one from Andorra I
toxe mi número de teléfono El de andorra
think they've also put if I go to the
también creo quean puesto si yo voy a
police station I show him the account that I
comisaría Le enseño la cuenta que la
have and I tell him this person is
tengo yo y le digo esta persona se está
dedicating himself to posting on social networks
dedicando a poner en redes sociales yo
what I am and I report him to the kid
lo que yo soy y lo denuncio al chaval
the police will take care of doing that or they
la policía se encarga de hacer eso o o
will tell me but since it's a
me van a decir ya pero como es una
new account and we don't know who it is so we ca
cuenta nueva y no sabemos Quién es pues
n't do
no podemos hacer
anything That tells you that
nada Eso te dice eso te
tells you man
dice tío
eh
eh lo
mine, mine, what we talked about on the
mío lo mío lo de lo que hablamos en la
sixth, he put it Apart from the complaints
sexta lo puso Aparte ya de las denuncias
that I filed at the police station at the
que puse yo en la comisaría en su
time eh Pablo
momento eh Pablo
reported it as a complaint and it was admitted for
lo lo denunció por querella y se admitió
processing before summer it was admitted for
a trámite antes de verano se admitió a
processing before summer I don't know if they
trámite antes de verano yo no sé si
are trying to locate him by
estarán intentando localizarlo por el
guy's number having the
número de tío teniendo el WhatsApp del
turkey's WhatsApp eh a Spanish phone number the
pavo eh un número de teléfono español el
WhatsApp
WhatsApp
eh here you have heard something I don't know anything
eh aquí tú has sabido algo Yo no sé nada
I don't know
yo no sé
anything I have already said it eh I have already said it eh
nada ya lo he dicho eh Ya lo he dicho eh
eh be careful because a melon is opening
eh cuidado porque se está abriendo un
a melon is being opened that they
melón se está abriendo un melón de que
are telling people that they can
le están diciendo a la gente que pueden
whenever they want to say something outrageous or
cuando quieran decir una barbaridad o
something that could harm them you say it
algo que les pueda perjudicar lo dices
from another account that is not your name and
desde otra cuenta que no es tu nombre y
nothing is going to happen to you eh be careful
y no te va a pasar nada eh cuidado que
that
se está lanzando ese
message is being sent strip your dick I want that
mensaje pela la [__] yo quiero que ese
kid's hair to fall out or rather for him to
chaval se le caiga el pelo o sea que él
say [ __ ] I messed with the
diga [__] me he metido con la persona
wrong person So since I want
equivocada Entonces como yo quiero que
that kid to say [ __ ] I messed with
ese chaval diga [__] me he metido con
the wrong person I don't know if I should
la persona equivocada no sé si
report him to the police because that's what
denunciarlo a la policía porque es lo
I feel like reporting to the
que me pide cuerpo denunciar a la
police but maybe I do report him
policía pero a lo mejor si lo denuncio
to the police and when I tell the
con la policía y cuando yo le digo al
other guy that I'm going to do it I say that I'm going to
otro ch que lo voy a doar digo que voy a
clean his face live I'm not even saying that I'm going to
asear su cara en directo que ni siquiera
tell him where he lives
digo que le vaya a decir ni dónde vive
or anything which he wouldn't even do I
ni nada cosa que ni siquiera haría
repeat again it's something I say in the
vuelvo a repetir es algo que digo en
heat of the moment so that the kid stops
caliente para que el chaval deje de
harassing me he's been harassing me for 8 hours do you
acosarme que lleva 8 horas acosándome
understand yes it doesn't happen I don't know if I have
entendéis sí no pasa No sé si lo he
explained it well I understood what I
explicado bien entendé a lo que me
mean not to him soon explain the
refiero no a el pronto expli cu el
time  and someone comes here to the
tiempo y que venga alguien aquí a la
call and argue with me
llamada y que discuta conmigo tanto
posting so much on Twitter posting so much on Twitter you
poner en Twitter tanto poner en Twitter
clash with the other that I have blocked
chocas po el otro que tengo bloqueado
with 20 ks so much that you post on Twitter
con 20 ks tanto que pones en Twitter
Chale balls And if you have so many things
Chale [__] Y si tantas cosas tienes
against me Get on disk to talk
en contra de mí Métete en disco a hablar
to me you don't do it because the
conmigo no lo haces porque a ti el
historical context doesn't benefit
contexto histórico te no te beneficia a
you the context that a kid has been
ti el contexto de que un chaval lleva 8
finishing 51 for 8 hours doesn't benefit you on
horas acando 51 no te beneficia a ti en
Twitter benefits you the 40
Twitter te beneficia el clip de 40
second clip of me getting horny with The
segundos de mí calentándome con El
kid so that all of Twitter hates me that
chaval para que todo Twitter me odie que
I don't care but from there comes a
me da igual pero que de ahí surge un tío
crazy guy from the multi-account head Exactly Ana
loco de la cabeza multicuenta Exacto Ana
but come on those are not excuses that I
pero vamos eso no son excusas que yo me
make up or anything I only took it to the
invento ni nada Solo llevo yo hasta el
end
final
and that's how it is you
y y es así
know from Benalmadena who [ __ ] and doxes my
sabes de benalmadena que coge y doxea mi
family man because of you for having a
familia tío por tu culpa por tener una
meme account and trying to load me with
cuenta de memes y intentar cargarme con
pitas with nonsense because of you if it
pitas con tonterías por vuestra culpa si
bothers you I am live every day
t molesta yo estoy todos los días en
from three in the afternoon to
directo de tres en puntos de la tarde a
8 in the evening you come and talk to me
8 de la tarde vienes y hablas conmigo
on discord  but it's that
por discord pero es que a ti no te
nothing bothers you you want virality that I ca
molesta nada tú quieres la viralidad que
n't change anymore the truth is
eso ya no puedo cambiarlo la verdad es
something that I can't change but I do
algo que no puedo cambiar pero sí que
want to report the person who is
quiero denunciar a la persona que está
putting the [ __ ] data man What happens is that I do
poniendo los [__] datos tío Lo que pasa
n't know IB going to do something because if you
que no s IB a hacer algo porque que si
think about it in the end I have made
lo pensáis al final yo que he hecho malo
a bad clip circulating of me insulting a
un clip rulando de mí insultando a un
kid that I would never have met or
chaval que yo nunca hubiera conocido ni
interacted with him if The
nunca hubiera interactuado con él si El
kid didn't thing for 8 hours straight
chaval no cosa durante 8 horas seguidas
that I give the guy a hug I don't know what I have
que le do un abrazo al tío No sé que he
done wrong to generate incite so much
hecho malo para generar incitar tanto
hatred towards my person I don't know why
odio hacia mi persona no sé por qué la
people value that I threaten a kid and do
gente valora que yo amenace un chaval y
n't value that that kid has been harassing me for 8 hours
no valore que ese chaval lleve 8 horas
I think there is a moment in the
acosándome creo que hay un momento del
clip that is going viral where the
clip que se está viralizando que el
kid tells me I'm going to leave eh And I
chaval me dice me voy a ir eh Y yo le
say thanks bro but let's see how
digo gracias bro pero vamos a ver cómo
you're going But if I want you to
que te vas Pero si yo quiero que te
leave if you've been harassing me for 8 hours If I do
vayas si llevas 8 horas acosándome Si yo
n't want you to exist in my live what the
no quiero que existas en mi directo qué
[ __ ] How am I going to leave dude go but
[__] Cómo que me voy a ir tío vete pero
now there's a guy  putting old data on the
ahora hay un tío poniendo datos en
internet that doesn't bother me
internet antiguos que no me molestan
but I already have a crazy person looking for where
pero ya tengo a un loco buscando donde
I live a crazy person doing something
yo vivo a un loco haciendo algo ilegal
really illegal with me because the first
de verdad conmigo porque la primera
phrase that I would say to everyone who is
frase que yo le diría a todo el mundo
disrespectful on Twitter is if you
que falta el respeto en Twitter es si tú
the choc p his mother
el choc p su madre en
actually well I wasn't going to say one thing
realidad bueno no iba a decir una cosa
but I'm not going to say it because I'm not going to
pero no la voy a decir porque no voy a
give any idea
dar idea
eh but well yes we have to be very
eh pero bueno sí hay que tener mucho
careful with the issue of people's data
cuidado con con el tema de los datos de
and other manga All the [ __ ]
la gente y demás manga Todos los [__]
morons from that podcast about the cat and
subnormales del podcast ese del gato y
the dog his [ __ ] mother in panties his
el perro su [__] madre en bragas sus
dead all the Twitter accounts with
muertos todas las cuentas de Twitter con
a LoL character with the former player
un personaje del LoL con el exjugador
of the cadi fbol club with more than 15 or
del cadi fúbol club con más de 15 o
20,000 followers who are dedicated to
20,000 seguidores que os dedicáis a
inciting on the internet the [ __ ] next
incitar al en internet la [__] próxima
time you want to talk about me put a
vez que queráis hablar de mí poner un
clip of mine [ __ ] do it but
clip mío de [__] madre hacerlo pero por
please with a little context so
favor con un poquito de contexto para
that later if you want to make some humor out
que luego si queréis hacer algo de humor
of it If you want to have a little
de eso Si queréis tener un un poco de
respect for the community try to
respeto a la comunidad intentar
release that respect and if you want to
desprender ese respeto y si queréis
make humor with something  what
hacer humor con algo lo
you know this is a reaction from
que sepáis que esto es una reacción de
Agustina to a guy who has
Agustina a un tío que lleva 8 horas
been accusing him for 8 hours I'm not saying I agree
acusándolo no digo que esté de acuerdo
but I understand you look good you win the
pero lo entiendo quedáis bien ganás el
humor the interactions and the [ __ ]
humor las interacciones y el [__]
respect which is that you forget
respeto que es que se os olvida el
respect which is the most important thing in this
respeto que los más importante de esta
life because everyone hates you guys there
vida porque a vosotros odia todo el
's a tweet that says okay on
mundo yo hay un tweet que dice vale en
Twitter with 20,000 25,000 fbs with
Twitter con 20,000 25000 fbs con
millions of impressions that makes me look
millones de impresiones que me pone a mí
like an arrogant kid with money
como un chaval arrogante con el dinero
says oh he's the typical one he's the example
dice aí es el típico es el vio ejemplo
money doesn't make values or I was
de el dinero no hace los valores o os lo
going to tell you dude I mean literally it was that one
iba a decir tío o sea literal fue ese
with the tweet that I found the clip
con el tweet que que encontré yo el clip
I know it says something like you have
yo que sé que pone algo como tienes
money but I already know that I know a
dinero pero ya sé que yo sé un lema de
shitty slogan it's a case similar to yours no
[__] es un caso parecido al tuyo no
Javi man mine goes a little further
Javi hombre el mío va un poco más allá
Ruben mine took the guy eh the guy
Rubén el mío cogió el tipo eh el tipo
who did it to me not only did he
que me lo hizo no solamente es que
put the address phone no no it's
pusiera la dirección teléfono no no es
that he took photos of my father of my mother
que cogió fotos de mi padre de mi madre
eh he published them for 8000 pages or rather
eh las publicó por 8000 páginas o sea
all of them  All the
todas las todas las páginas de anuncios
online dating and
que existan en internet de contactos y
second hand ads and things like that were published
de segunda mano y cosas así las publicó
with my parents' information, my
con los datos de mis padres con mis
information, telling us that we're pedophiles and
datos poniéndonos que somos pedófilos y
stuff like that,
cosas por el estilo
but it's really heavy, eh, I mean, my thing is that
pero muy heavy eh o sea lo mío que tú
you say what can you expect
ante eso dices tú qué qué puedes esperar
from any crime committed
de de cualquier delito que cometan
against you on the internet, dude,
contra ti en internet tío si es que
literally, my thing was to put the
literalmente lo mío era para meter al
guy in jail, dude, and it's not like, well,
tío en la cárcel tío y no es decir Bueno
the issue has passed, one has gone,
pues se ha pasado el tema se ha ido una
no, no, no, no, no, my thing, I went to the
no no no no no no lo mío yo fui a la
police station, I reported that in 2020
comisaría denunci eso que fue el 2020
because it seems to me that it was like before the
porque me parece que fue una como antes
summer, a
de verano una
complaint and it seems to me that later I filed another one
denuncia y me suena que luego puse Otra
like in January, almost a year, which would be
como en enero por ahí casi al año que
2021, I can't imagine, and now in
sería 2021 no me imagino y ahora en el
2023, when I already knew Pablo,
2023 ya cuando ya conociendo a Pablo
Pablo said this, this, this, I'll put it
Pablo dijo esto esto esto lo pongo yo
as you want now and he put it in and put it in,
como queréis ya y lo metió y lo metió
that's the one who called in the car, he
ese es el que llamaba en el coche
called, let's say it was, it was on another
llamaba vamos es que era Era er a otro
level, I mean, in the face of that you say what  They
nivel o sea es que ante eso tú dices qué
have to do to you what they have to
te tienen que hacer qué te tienen que
do to you on the internet so you
hacer en internet para que
know, I mean, yes, yes, yes I'm already
sabes o sea es que si si si ya os estoy
telling you here publicly and
diciendo Yo aquí públicamente y ya os
I'm already telling you that my videos and my But not my
digo yo que mis vídeos y mi Pero no mi
video but my video my intervention in
vídeo sino mi vídeo mi intervención en
the sixth, I mean, people have seen that
la sexta o sea eso lo ha visto gente
[ __ ] people of the police have seen that and
[__] gente de policía eso lo ha visto
you you say but yes, yes, it's
gente y ya tú tú dices pero si si si es
that I have filed two complaints at the
que le he puesto dos denuncias en la
police station the lawyer has
comisaría de policía el abogado le ha
filed a complaint in court I
puesto una querella en el juzgado yo
also went to court in between if
también fui al juzgado de por medio si
I'm not mistaken man they haven't even
no me equivoco tío es que ni me han
called me nor have they called me the only thing I
llamado ni me han llamado lo único que
knew was when Pablo filed a
supe fue ya cuando Pablo lo puso por
complaint that they notified him that it had been
querella que que le notificaron el
admitted for processing and that's it. I
haberlo admitido a trámite ya está
mean, what the [ __ ] do you have to
O sea qué qué [__] tienes que
do, Podemos, you [ __ ] [ __ ] person, to
hacer podemita de [__] subnormal de
say Okay, I'll elbow you How many
decir Bueno te meto un codazo Cuántas
times, kids, have I remained calm
veces chavales yo me a quedado tranquilo
like this How many times have you said
así Cuántas veces habéis dicho vosotros
in this live broadcast that money is discredited
en este directo que es desprestigiado el
and I have said that money is
dinero y he dicho que el dinero es una
[ __ ] and for me money is credit
[__] y para mí el dinero es crédito
like a video game thanks to  God I
como un videojuego gracias a Dios lo
have it, I don't care but I don't
tengo no me preocupa pero yo no me
feel more than anyone else for having money nor
siento más que nadie por tener dinero ni
less than anyone else for having money How many
menos que nadie por tener dinero Cuántas
times do I have to say it on Stream I have
veces lo tengo que decir en Stream lo he
said it many more times that let's see he uses
dicho muchas más veces que a ver utiliza
uses money many times as if he
utiliza muchas veces el dinero como que
has more power than people for having
tiene más poder que la gente por tener
money eh I have heard it on
dinero eh yo lo he escuchado ya en
many
muchas
occasions eh Don't brag Maybe
ocasiones eh No presumir A lo mejor de
the things that he has that I also tell you
las cosas que tiene que también te digo
one thing that with how young he is it is evident
una cosa que con lo joven que es se nota
that he has had maybe I don't know if it will be I don't
que ha tenido a lo mejor no sé si será
know if he has an older brother But I
no sé si tiene algú hermano mayor Pero
imagine it will be his mother she will have been
me imagino que será la madre habrá
very aware of him because with how
estado muy pendiente de él porque con lo
young he is how young
joven que él con lo joven que es
anyone loses their mind with
cualquiera pierde la cabeza con el
money and and makes a mistake eh makes a mistake he goes
dinero y y mete la pata eh mete la pata
bankrupt and and he goes bankrupt and it ends badly
se arruina y y se arruina él y acaba mal
He is worth it And yes it is true that he has
Él vale Y sí que es verdad que que tiene
his nice car I would be missing more if he didn't have it, I would be missing
su coche bonito Me faltaría más que no
a Renault
tuviera faltaría que tuviera un Renault
5 If he likes to have a nice car you
5 Si a él le gusta tener un coche bonito
understand and he has investments he has
me entiendes y tiene inversiones tiene
companies I mean he doesn't have money saved you
empresas O sea no tiene dinero ahorrado
understand that what he has used it
me entiendes que lo que lo ha utilizado
for, not to show off but he has
para no no para vasilar sino que lo ha
used it  as on some occasions he has
utilizado como en alguna ocasión lo ha
used it as if he has more power
utilizado como como que tiene más poder
than people for having money, I
que la gente por tener dinero yo te
report you, I spend all the money I
denuncio me gasto todo el dinero que
have and I sink you judicially, I don't know what
tengo y te hundo judicialmente no sé qué
And it's like money is not always what
Y es como el dinero no siempre es lo que
gives you more or less power okay okay
te da más o menos poder vale vale
obviously tearing your life easier
evidentemente tearse la vida más fácil
but oh well
pero bueno
m anyway he is a kid I think he is
m en fin es un chaval creo que tiene
like 23 not 24
como 23 no 24
years old the times that I have threatened
años las veces que he amenazado a
someone with Gar my money to screw in
alguien con Gar mi dinero en [__] en la
life and when I have done the second it has
vida y cuando he hecho lo segundo ha
been because that person was
sido porque esa persona me estaba
screwing my life up and anyone in my
jodiendo la vida a mí y cualquiera en mi
situation would do the same thing I hate
situación haría lo mismo que yo odio el
money that I don't even know how much money I have that I don't care
dinero que no sé ni cuánto dinero Tengo
that I don't move for
que me da igual que no me muevo por
money and I have never done it not just anyone
pasta y lo he hecho nunca no cualquiera
starts threatening to dox others
se pone a amenazar de doxear a los demás
no of course No Santi of course it is not
no desde luego No Santi desde luego no
usually the people who receive support
suele ser la gente que que recibe aposo
for 9 hours 8 hours bro
durante 9 horas 8 horas bro
8 hours that my clip lasts 40 seconds that
8 horas que mi clip dura 40 segundos que
I curse everything is true and that I
me cago en todo es verdad y que la
threaten her is true 40 seconds to
amenazo es verdad 40 segundos para
vent that it has been 8 hours
desfogar que lleva 8 horas
like this  8 hours my brother 8 hours 8
así 8 horas mi hermano 8 horas 8 horas
hours are you not aware bro are you not aware 8 hours like this or tomorrow morning I'm going to go to the [ __ ] police station I'm going to show this past I'm going to explain I'm going to ask What do I have to do
voy a pregun Qué tengo que hacer en
in my situation I'm going to
lugar en mi situación lo voy a
do it tomorrow morning I'm going to go to the
hacer mañana va a ir por la mañana a la
police station I'm going to go Don't tell me that because I'm
comisaría voy a ir No me digas eso que
really going and I see it you
de verdad porque voy y lo veo os
imagine that I'm going with Teresa Alceo's microphone
imagináis que voy con el micro de Teresa
Agustn What did she tell you What did she tell you
alceo Agustín Qué te ha dicho la Qué te
What did the
ha dicho la Qué te ha dicho la
police tell you about the niping I just realized
policía del niping me acabo de dar
you didn't tell me aa Lorena I just
cuenta tú no me ha dicho aa Lorena me
realized that I got this
cuenta que me ha llegado esto
too
también
eye Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey Oy Hey I'm
ojo Oye oye oye
going to go I'm going to sing a
Oye me voy a ir me voy a ir a cantar una
battle Now when I finish the live
batalla Ahora cuando termine el directo
eh I mean I'm going there to sing a battle
eh o sea me voy ahí a cantar una batalla
Now when I finish the live eh Hey
Ahora cuando termine el directo eh Oye
but he has he has
pero es que tiene es que tiene
quality this guy in the store
calidad el nota este en la tienda
eh even with more serious cases
eh incluso con casos más graves la
justice is done  not even the slightest
justicia hac ni las más mínimas
investigations Yeah but now you
investigaciones Sí pero ahora tú le
tell someone stupid and and
dices a uno tonto y
and they even feature you on
y y te sacan hasta en el
ABC
ABC
family Well yeah alne well yes I'm going to
familia Pues sí alne pues sí se lo voy a
tell him to send more things and or or I'm going
decir que mande más cositas y o o le voy
to ask for a big order so that
a pedir un pedido grande para para que
you can wear it Listen I'm going
os lo pongáis que Escucha
to have dinner I'm going to have dinner to go to
voy a cenar voy a cenar para irme a
telesalseo come on I'm going to give it my all
telesalseo venga va voy a echarle huevo
and I'm going to go to telesalseo I'm going to
y voy a ir a telesalseo voy a ir a
give it my all and we're going to go to telesalseo I
echarle huevo y vamos a ir a telesalseo
saw to give it my all and we're going to go to
vi a echarle huevo y vamos a ir a
telesalseo Okay family,
telesalseo Bueno familia
more or less this that has been today
pues más o menos esto que ha sido hoy
would be the day to day now of the salsera
sería el día a día ahora de la salsería
with the difference that when there are
con la diferencia de que cuando haya
bigger topics than right now there aren't any
temas más gordo que ahora mismo no los
in the salsera Well there will be many
hay en la salsería Pues habrá muchos
days that maybe the live instead of
días que a lo mejor el directo en vez de
starting at 8 and ending at 10 it will
empezar a las 8 y termina a las 10
start at 8 and end at 1 because
empiece a las 8 y termine a la 1 porque
we have a lot of things to see or I have a
tengamos muchas cosas que ver o que
lot of things in the canijo and in the
tenga muchas cosas en el canijo y en el
telesalseo I don't have them and we stay here you
telesalseo no tenga y nos quedemos aquí
understand or we start  directly
me entiendes o empecemos directamente
for example when we do the
por ejemplo cuando hagamos lo de lo de
delox thing in the coming days it
delox estos días que vienen pues
probably won't be at 8 of course
seguramente no va a ser a las 8 claro
eh No we
eh No el aroba lo vamos a dejar el ara
're going to leave the ara we're going to leave it Javier canijo as a souvenir but maybe there will be days when in the live shows I won't have to go to telesalseo and say Okay so I'm going then at 10 10:30 for canijo instead of
10:30 para el canijo en vez de para en
instead of at 8 okay but more or less
vez de a las 8 vale pero más o menos
this would be the rhythm okay we're missing the
este sería el ritmito vale falta el
newscast we're missing the newscast since
noticiero falta el noticiero que como
we've been live now the
hemos estado en directo ahora pues el
newscast hasn't been published because we've been
noticiero se no se ha publicado porque
here live and then
hemos estado aquí en directo y entonces
the newscast is The newscast will be
el noticiero se El Noticiero se
published in a while in a while
publicará en en un ratte en un
But well I don't see it bad eh eh the
rete Pero bueno mal no lo veo eh eh el
live show has worked more or less the same
directo ha funcionado más o menos igual
yes it's true that a little bit
sí que es verdad que un poquito más
later it works better but as I told you it
tarde funciona mejor pero ya os digo
will depend on if I have a topic on the other
dependerá de si tengo tema en el otro
side or or whatever
lado o o lo que
but we're going to lift it we're going to
pero lo vamos a levantar lo vamos a
lift the two channels the telesalseo
levantar los dos canales el telesalseo
the results are already being seen in  the
ya se están viendo los resultados en el
telesalseo the results are looking
telesalseo se están viendo los
very good you and here it's that
resultados muy buenos tú y aquí es que
the topics are not helping either
los temas tampoco es que estén ayudando
people say Oh how weak the
la gente dice Ay qué flojitas están las
visits are but it's that the topics are not
visitas pero es que los temas tampoco
helping but next week next
están ayudando pero la semana que viene
week the topics will
la semana que viene los temas sí van a
help
ayudar
eh if next week it doesn't work the topics will not
eh si la semana que viene no va no
help I mean with the topics that there are next week
ayudan los temas o sea con los temas que
no no with next week the topics will work but
hay la semana que viene no no con la
with next week and and then the other one
con la semana que viene y y luego la
joining and then the other one
otra empalmando y luego la otra
joining the
empalmando si van a ayudar los
topics will help but it's what I'm telling you I mean
temas pero es lo que os digo o sea
depending on not only the
dependiendo de de no solamente de los
topics but if I have direct on the other side I
temas sino de si tengo en el otro lado
don't have it because if I didn't have
directo no lo tengo porque si no tuviera
direct on telesalseo I wouldn't have to
directo en telesalseo no tendría ahora
leave now maybe I can stay
que irme ya a lo mejor me puedo quedar
an hour more but it's that we wouldn't
una hora más pero es que tampoco
have many here either We wouldn't have
tendríamos aquí muchas No tendríamos
much more to see the
mucho más que ver la
truth tomorrow I will come here surely
verdad mañana me vendré por aquí segur
also at the same time as today
ente también a la misma hora que hoy
Oh no tomorrow I have an MRI
Ah no mañana tengo una resonancia
you I don't remember what time it was but let's
tú no me acuerdo a qué hora era pero
go at 8 I won't be here no way
vamos a las 8 no estaré aquí ni de coña
I have an MRI you tomorrow at
tengo una resonancia tú mañana por la
afternoon tomorrow there won't be any videos
tarde mañana no habrá ni vídeos
probably tomorrow there will be almost no
seguramente mañana no habrá casi ni
videos neither on telesalseo nor here
vídeos ni en telesalseo ni aquí
eh tomorrow there will be almost no video an
eh mañana no habrá casi ni vídeo una
MRI in the afternoon you the
resonancia por la tarde tú la
preparation and all that stuff in the in
preparación y todoo el rollo ese por la
the afternoon Well I don't know what time I'll
por la tarde Pues no sé a qué hora
come I'll come to react to the
vendré vendré a reaccionar al
rewind I'll come to react to the rewind
rewind vendré a reaccionar al rewind
tomorrow but I don't know what time I don't know what
mañana pero no sé a qué hora no sé a qué
time [ __ ] I would have liked to do it
hora [__] me hubiera gustado hacerlo
here at 8 well Ana because I have
aquí en a las 8 pues Ana porque yo tengo
cron's disease and they do checks on me
enfermedad de cron y me hacen controles
Nothing bad is happening or anything but they do
No pasa nada malo ni nada pero me hacen
checks on me so well that's it we'll
controles pues bueno ya está ya nos
adapt
adaptaremos
as best we can tomorrow okay people Thanks
como podamos mañana vale gente Gracias
for the support I'm going to telesalseo
por el apoyo me voy para telesalseo
in half an hour or so I'm going to have
dentro de media hora más o menos voy a
dinner and I'm going to telesalseo
cenar y me voy para telesalseo
and around here in a little while the
y por aquí dentro de un ratito estará el
news will be on okay So nothing a kiss and
noticiero vale Así que nada un beso y
we'll talk hearts bye
hablamos corazones chao
[Music]
[Música]
bye ev
chao ev